(This show features indirect advertisements.)
(Running Man)
(It's early morning, and people are busy heading to work.)
Hello.
(The office is still empty,)
(and Manager Yu is the first to clock in.)
They should be here by 8:30am,
but no one is here yet.
Minus five hours, so the starting time is 8:30am.
(Last week)
What?
(They must start filming at 8:30am, which is extra early for them.)
1:30pm was better.
(He's the only one who is pleased.)
(Morning person Manager Yu arrived 5 minutes early.)
There are lots of nice things in the pantry.
(He took one.)
What are these gold bars?
The CEO gave your team a bonus.
(The CEO generously gave them 30 1kg gold bars.)
What company pays bonuses in gold bars these days?
(Manager Yu, who is next in line, will hand them out to the team.)
You will hand them out.
Oh, me? Okay, understood.
(Knocking)
- Hello. - Hello.
(The employees start to arrive.)
- Take a seat. - Hello.
- If you don't mind... - Yes?
- What company is this? - What?
What do we do here?
I was just told to come to work.
- You came not knowing your job? - Well, yes.
Get out.
- Shall I drag him out? Come along. - Yes. He's leaving.
How can you come to work not knowing what we do?
(He has the looks of a chairman but the awareness of a newbie.)
- What I meant was... - Leave.
- Ye Eun, you can sit. - Okay.
Come in later.
How can someone come to work without knowing what he does?
(Making another attempt right away)
I know what we do now.
What do we do?
It's a trading company.
- You can sit. - Is it really?
(He gets approved for once.)
- Can I... - Make me some Solomon's seal tea.
(It turns out Employee Jee keeps the office stocked.)
- Well, I... - What's the matter?
- My experience... - How many years...
I'll have green tea, please.
I'll have kombu tea, please.
- Kombu tea. - Kombu tea.
You're my friend's daughter.
(Attempting a skit)
- Didn't we start here together? - I've watched you grow up...
(Rejecting)
since you were this little.
(The hierarchy is messed up.)
- Whether she's your friend's... - Yes.
(Setting him straight)
daughter or relative, it doesn't matter.
- I'm sorry. - This is a workplace, not a club.
Please put in some effort.
(Seok Sam gets picked on from all over.)
Why did you come in with your shirt all open?
(An undershirt office look)
He's claiming to be ATEEZ's SAN today.
(Breathing in and out)
His armpits!
(Wriggling)
Seriously!
(The Northern Duke melting every woman's heart)
His armpits!
(The Belly Duke killing the office vibe)
- Seriously... - He's the worst.
His armpits!
(The Northern Duke vs. the Belly Duke)
- Seriously... - He's the worst.
(Grimacing)
Seriously...
- Also, - Yes?
it's not a wave. It goes like this.
(As they bust out awful dance moves on a Monday morning...)
- A chest pop? - It's a chest pop.
Good morning!
- Goodness. - Hello.
(Employee Kook arrives loudly.)
- It's here! - Lovely morning.
- Okay. - Nice to meet you.
- Hello. - That hurts.
Hello, I'm Song Ji Hyo, a new hire.
- It's here. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
(The office is quickly filled up.)
Are we doing this again?
- This way... - Is this my place?
(Everyone made it to work on time.)
- Is it... - Where is my seat?
- We have designated seats. - Is this my seat?
Hold on.
What's with the shorts?
- You... - Do you think you're in Hawaii?
(Employee Ha is wearing a breezy outfit.)
- You're... - Are you kidding?
- That's disrespectful. - Well...
- Look around here. - Yes.
Look at how everyone else is dressed.
(They're all in stuffy office outfits.)
- Look around here. - Yes.
Look at how everyone else is dressed.
(He's come to work looking like he's in Hawaii.)
- There are limits. - Seriously.
Isn't this a fashion company?
- His mindset... - What?
This is a trading company.
- Look at this gold bar. - You don't even know your company.
(A suspicious trading company that gives away gold bars)
What's this?
A single gold bar costs around 200,000 dollars.
- Is this a smuggling company? - Do we smuggle gold bars?
Is this the mafia?
- Hold on. - Hey...
(Manager Yu gets upset with the careless remark.)
Smuggling was just a joke,
but the mafia was a little much.
Should I take off his pants?
(Taking action)
- Also, - I think we should.
(Knocking)
- the vacation... Who is it? - What is it?
- Why does the Running Man shoot... - What?
- start so early now? - It's Kang Hoon.
- Kang Hoon! - He's here.
(The real new hires are here.)
- This guy... - The new hires...
- Hello. - Hello.
(Shy)
- Goodness. - It's Hye Jun.
You're here.
(The one-day new hires are looking stunning!)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hye Jun and Woo Min. - Right.
We have new faces.
(Actor Kang Hoon, Actress Kim Hye Jun,)
Woo Min. Nice to meet you.
(Actor Cha Woo Min)
- It's been a while, Hye Jun. - Hello.
- We've never met. - Hello.
Have you been well?
(The office lights up with the familiar faces...)
Okay, okay!
(and the handsome new one.)
So you're the new hires.
- They're our new hires. - Yes.
Why don't you introduce yourselves?
Okay. Well, I...
used to be one of the rented members,
so I'm not a new hire. I'm back after seven months.
He's showing off.
He's showing off right from the start.
I'm back after seven months.
- Hello, I'm Kang Hoon. - You've gotten quite confident.
- Yes. - You've gotten quite confident.
(A tough-looking coward recognized by other cowards)
He's a coward!
- What's wrong with him? - What's wrong?
(Hoon's lower body is weaker than a newborn fawn's.)
- Kang Hoon. - What's wrong, Kang Hoon?
Why are you circling in the same place?
(Talking back)
- Because you're not moving! - You should go back and forth!
(His body is weak, but he always talks back.)
Let's stop here.
- With passion. You should run! - With passion. Of course.
(The youngest member who always spoke his mind...)
That style doesn't work...
(among the tough older members.)
on me. I'm the type who does well when I'm praised.
- I'll take care of it. - Applause.
(Kook's nemesis, who's not afraid of standing up to him)
I'm glad you came all grown up.
(Ye Eun is especially happy to see him.)
What is it, Ye Eun?
I'm sorry, Hoon.
(His ex-fling starts by apologizing.)
Why all of a sudden?
They...
- Did you hear the news? - I did.
- I read about it in the news. - She's...
- In the news. - Why are you suddenly apologizing?
(Her face is so red that it shows through her makeup.)
I feel sorry.
Her face turned red.
- What's the matter with you? - Why are you blushing?
- Why are you getting all red? - Ye Eun!
- What's up with you? - You're being weird.
(It seems like they still have some unfinished business.)
- Do you still have feelings? - Even her ears are red.
- Goodness. - I mean,
I think he liked me.
- But I was too... - I was completely used by her.
(Hoon was used in her love game.)
- I was born in 1991. - Ye Eun, go quickly!
(Ye Eun's dimpled crush who made her Mondays better...)
(with the perfect 3-year age gap)
What's going on?
- What's going on? - What's going on?
Why are you holding hands? What's going on?
- I don't have a crush on him. - Me neither.
(She took full advantage of him and found her true love.)
- I just like him a little. - Just a little.
I'm really sorry. It just happened that way.
It's okay. It was such great news.
It was such great news.
(I like it better this way.)
(Somehow, her ex-fling even looks relieved.)
- "It's okay." - He's happy.
I really...
read the news article while clapping.
Kang Hoon said...
he could now come to Running Man comfortably.
- It had been a while... - Right.
(It was nice to come to work without worrying about the fling.)
since I came running to the Running Man shoot.
Nice. First of all,
- please greet everyone, Hye Jun. - Right.
Hye Jun came here seven years ago. You all know that, right?
(Hye Jun is back after 7 years, since she visited in 2019.)
Right.
Hold on!
(25-year-old Hye Jun)
(The easily-scared and innocent Hye Jun,)
(who was in her 20s back then,)
I'm so tired. I need you to die already.
(has returned with a more mature aura.)
- Hye Jun became a star now. - Not at all.
- She's become very... - You don't know me.
Of course, I know you.
- Every Korean knows who you are. - What's her surname?
- What's my surname? - What's her surname?
- Pardon? - What's my surname?
We can get to know each other little by little.
It's even written right there.
(Staff ID, Kim Hye Jun)
(He didn't even take the open book.)
- It was right in front of you. - He didn't put in any effort.
You're not even trying to get to know her.
(Employee Jee is always a step behind.)
- You're not even trying. - You have the same surname.
- I know it. - Nice to meet you all.
Right.
- I'm happy you became successful. - I know, right?
Please take good care of me.
How old do you think Hye Jun is?
(Hey, Seok Sam.)
(Sparkling eyes)
She just looks...
(Startled at her intense gaze)
She's looking at me with her eyes wide open like that.
- She's trying to look young. - How old do I look?
(Eyes wide)
Around 27?
Twenty-seven?
- She's 32. - Really?
- That doesn't make sense. - She looks really young.
(Her baby face makes it impossible to guess.)
- No way. - Hye Jun...
was born in 1995.
- So she's around Ye Eun's age? - She's in her 20s.
- If she was born in 1995... - She's not around Ye Eun's age.
Ye Eun is way older.
- I'm only a year older. - She looks...
(Ye Eun, born in 1994)
- way older than her. - Do you want your gums to collapse?
(Getting startled)
My gums to collapse?
(A terrifying warning on his gums)
Hey!
We're both employees here. She wants to make my gums...
- That's... - Ye Eun!
Ye Eun!
Do you have a number of the gum series?
- No... - You're coming up with more.
(It's a gum series just for Ssaebssaeb.)
- It just applies to Yang Se Chan. - For Yang Se Chan.
He might get...
- a toothpaste commercial offer. - But...
- He'd need to pull out his teeth. - His face is already falling apart.
- If his gums fall apart too, - Right.
(Snorting)
won't everything fall apart?
- Hye Jun... - You're shocked, aren't you?
What's wrong?
"His face is already falling apart. If his gums fall apart too..."
(His heart sank before his gums.)
You're saying that as if you think it's true.
You can't lose your gum when your face is already falling apart.
- This has no impact on him. - Right.
Right, please introduce yourself.
(The last new hire is Woo Min.)
Cha Woo Min.
Right.
Nice to meet you all.
I'm Cha Woo Min.
He's got...
- the old-school crush vibe. - He's got the vibe.
(A classic first-crush look with refined features)
He's good-looking.
- I was born in 2000. I'm 27. - You're 27?
(Surprised)
- He's 27. - People born in 2000 are 27?
- Where were you born? - I...
- Pardon? - I was just curious.
(The auntie fan is curious about the boy's hometown.)
Ji Hyo!
Why are you suddenly asking Woo Min questions?
Well,
he's cute.
(Pure intentions of a mom)
- He's like your son. - He's your son!
- Why did you talk in that tone? - I mean...
- "He's cute." - He's just cute.
(Seriously)
He's cute.
I was born in Busan.
(Kind)
- Hold on. - Bu...
- Busan! - Yes, Busan.
- Busan... - Stop it, you fake!
(Employee Ha, who was born in Germany, reacts to "Busan.")
- You're from Busan! - Are you from Busan?
Come on, you're not from Busan.
- You're fake. - You...
You've picked the right side.
- Side... - I also live in Mapo-gu.
- Really? - Hey!
(I found my little brother.)
We're Mapo seagulls.
- You live in Mapo-gu? - Yes.
(Intercepting the handshake)
- Hi. - He's great.
- What's with your tone? - Hey...
(She does her best to force a connection with the young boy.)
Seeing Ji Hyo like this...
So you used to be an athlete.
- Really? - You used to swim.
Swim?
I used to swim,
and I also did judo for about four years.
(Even Jong Kook approved of his amazing physique.)
- Now... - Let's go.
That's right.
(He's very excited.)
(He'll be overpowering the members with his insane physique.)
You really worked out...
(Claiming dibs on his favorite younger brother)
- That's why you're so well-built. - a lot.
Anyway, Woo Min...
- They filmed a drama together. - Recently...
(The title of the new drama of these good-looking people...)
- What's the title? - The title.
It's "My Bias, My Boss."
(is "My Bias, My Boss.")
- "My Bias, My Boss." - "My Bias, My Boss."
- That's why we're employees. - My bias.
- "My Bias, My Boss." - So you're the boss,
(It's an office romance drama about accidentally becoming...)
- and you're... - So it's a love triangle.
(an employee of a bias.)
- A love triangle. - I'm the CEO.
(Will these fresh new hires be able to become...)
- Nice. - Right.
(the favorite employee of the day?)
Okay, so...
since you're all here,
I'll hand out the gold bars.
- You'll just give them to us? - For coming to work?
- Yes. - Thank you.
(The gold bar bonus makes it worth coming to work.)
Once you come in to work...
- Thank you. - I'll give it to you...
since you came to work.
- This is just... - Thank you.
(You can earn 200 thousand dollars just by showing up at this company.)
It was coated in gold.
- It was coated in gold. - It's heavy.
What kind of work will we do?
Please stand up for a moment.
(Before that...)
- Please stand up. - Why?
(Haha gets singled out for asking a question.)
- You've been targeted. - Seriously.
- This is too short. - Hot pants at the office?
Your pants are almost...
- as long as your underwear. - I mean...
What is this? Where did you get such pants?
(Shorts so short that they're hard to look at)
- This isn't appropriate. - Why are you making an issue...
out of my clothes?
Isn't the dress code casual?
It's not.
What do you take our company for?
This company is seriously...
What about this company?
Quit, then.
(They start to pick on him, using his outfit as an excuse.)
You can just leave.
- You're always free to quit. - Just quit.
Someone will replace you.
- That's right. - You can leave.
Why should I quit for wearing shorts?
(Fiercely standing up to his seniors)
- I... - Why are you acting so cocky?
(Smacking)
(Bad Boy steps in to teach him a lesson.)
Why are you acting so cocky?
Should I go back to my old self?
(Even the junior joins in on the bullying.)
- How rude of you to talk... - Come on.
- Se Chan. - Yes.
(Loving it)
- You can't swear. - Right. I won't swear.
Take your seat.
- He's acting so cocky. - Please sit down.
(A beautiful workplace culture where hierarchy is long gone)
- Okay. - Today's race is called...
Goal: The Favorite Employee.
The employees have to collect...
(You need to gather as much gold as you can to win!)
the gold bars handed out by the CEO.
- The person who collects... - Hold on.
- Yes? - Give me my gold bar.
What?
(A gold bar goes missing before the job even begins.)
I only have mine.
- Why are you blaming me? - Is yours missing?
It just started. Why are you doing this?
(The junior next door has a bad habit.)
This is mine. I don't have it.
- Stop making me annoyed. - Check Seok Jin.
You're getting to watch...
how it is in Running Man. You should watch out.
- Is it really gone? - You should hide it.
(He clumsily tries to hide the gold in tissue paper.)
Thank you.
We're showing them everything.
(Wrapping it)
Gold bars can be earned through missions,
(Give it!)
with varying amounts awarded based on the results.
You can also earn them when you're voted...
the favorite employee.
The gold bars handed out by Manager Yu...
will be kept in your personal safes.
- Personal safes? - Okay.
We'll have a meeting to earn gold bars...
- in another location. - Okay!
(They head off for the mission that will give them gold.)
Let's move!
This gold bar mission is called...
(The first mission that can win them gold)
Heated Debate Battle.
(Goal: The Favorite Employee, Mission 1, Heated Debate Battle)
- What is it about? - We love debates.
The two teams will debate...
(They will start a debate based on office topics.)
topics that office workers can relate to.
Out of the two answers,
you'll debate whichever one gets selected at random.
Whichever team receives the most staff votes...
when the debate ends...
- will score points. - Are we playing in teams?
From our experience,
the staff doesn't vote based on who's more logical.
- Whoever's louder? - They lean more toward emotion.
(The staff has a soft spot for emotional appeals.)
- I think he's right. - Right?
Also, whatever Jae Seok says...
- Jae Seok? - Just Jae Seok?
Did you call him by his first name?
(He's the manager.)
Here, the rest of you each get one.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Everyone except the clueless Seok Jin gets a gold bar.)
- Thank you. - Gosh.
- No matter what... - Seriously?
- How is this fair? - We got a gold bar for no reason.
Let me show you...
- the workplace hierarchy. - This is insane.
(Glancing)
(Seok Jin helps himself to one.)
Can you believe it?
- Here. - Thank you.
I knew it.
(She is bright, not knowing about the embezzlement.)
Please sit down.
You saw how office hierarchy works, right?
Talk about a clear reward and punishment.
(Manager Yu is great at giving them retail therapy.)
What the team leader says goes a long way, doesn't it?
(Complaining)
That's for sure. Right?
- That's what we just saw. - That's enough.
(Employee Jee has no one to turn to.)
- Seriously? You guys... - He has no one to lean on.
- The reward paid off. - I love it.
(Pleased)
The gold carries weight, doesn't it?
You'll receive gold bars based on how well you do.
(The gold bars will be rewarded based on the outcome.)
- Sure. - Jae Seok, Seok Jin,
Haha, Hoon, and Hye Jun are a team.
- Okay. - Let's do this.
Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, Se Chan,
- Ye Eun, and Woo Min are a team. - Nice.
- Let's begin the first debate. - Sure thing.
Please reveal the debate topic.
(The debate topic is revealed.)
- Yes or no? - Whoever is more logical...
If work begins at 9am, can you just show up at 9am?
(If work begins at 9am, can you just show up at 9am?)
(A: Yes, B: No)
(The morning commute is always hectic.)
(Is arriving right on the dot acceptable or not?)
I made it just in time.
- Why not? - No way.
- Of course not. - That's not allowed.
- No way. - Seriously?
- Why not? - That's because...
(With opinions divided...)
We don't know which position we're taking yet.
- You'll choose randomly. - But share your thoughts.
(They decide to share opinions before picking teams.)
- What's your personal opinion? - B!
I pick side B.
(Ye Eun's opinion: B. You can't show up at 9am.)
- Why? - Why?
Even if our call time is 8:30am,
we're expected to arrive by 8:20am.
- Of course. - That's because 8:30am...
- is when work actually starts. - That's right.
If work starts at 9am, you should get...
- That's right. - to the office...
- You're smart for a Gen Zer. - by at least 8:55am.
- Hold on. - She's a smart cookie.
(The Gen Z employee sounds smart for once.)
You sound kind of dumb, if you ask me.
Eat it, Grandma!
- Hold on. - Well...
(The old man makes personal attacks.)
- Mister. - Grandma Jee!
- You can't call her dumb. - That was a bit mean.
(He loses his right to speak due to the malicious insults.)
What's wrong with showing up at 9am...
if that's when you're supposed to be there?
Office hours are typically from 9 to 6.
That's 9am to 6pm.
- Right. - Those are the office hours.
- Exactly. - How can you show up...
right on the dot...
and start working the second you sit down?
- He's right. - If you can, then nine is fine.
(Jong Kook's opinion: You need to arrive earlier to start at 9am.)
- Exactly. - But that's never the case.
If work begins at 9am, I can show up at 9am and...
- Are you hearing this brat? - What?
- His tone and that expression... - Jong Kook, please.
- I'm right. - This is only a debate.
(Kim Thug mercilessly takes out his favorite little brother.)
- But... - I'm right.
You can't call him a brat during a debate.
- His tone... - Is this because I missed soccer?
Of course not. I'm just saying that your tone and expression...
(He must be really upset about the soccer game no-show incident.)
come across as bratty.
One member from each team...
Do we have to defend the position we choose?
(They will stand for the opinion that they drew and start debating.)
- That's how it works. - That's right.
Mr. Shorts, go ahead.
(The SAN-wannabe is pumping his chest again.)
Like SAN.
- SAN? - Like SAN.
(Disgusted)
- That's not it. - That's not how you do it.
(The "Bad" Challenge couldn't avoid being killed.)
That's not it. The hand travels down.
(Watching closely)
You two are becoming more and more alike.
- Hey, don't say things like that. - Who's that supposed to offend?
- I don't want to age like him. - Me neither.
(Killing two birds with his innocent face)
- Just choose one, mister. - One, two...
- I've been thinking that too. - B.
- No way. - That's not allowed.
(B. You can't show up at 9am.)
Our team officially argues...
- against it. - Against it.
(A. You can show up at 9am.)
- What? - We support it.
- No way. - Let's try to convince them.
(A. You can show up at 9am. B. You can't show up at 9am.)
It's A versus B.
- All right. - Let the debate begin.
(A. You can show up at 9am.)
- Ready... - Hear me out.
Why do people have to be so strict about time?
- I mean... - Exactly.
Unbelievable.
(Changing his stance right away)
- It's wrong. - We support B.
Are you hearing this brat?
(Just 1 minute ago)
- B. - Why be so rigid?
(B. You can't show up at 9am.)
Arriving ten minutes early...
- is common sense. - Of course.
It shouldn't even be five minutes. That's just common sense.
- It's an unwritten social rule. - Even when I meet up with people,
since buses and trains can run late and traffic can be heavy,
(You can be late, so you need to show up 10 minutes early.)
I leave early aiming to arrive 30 minutes ahead of time.
- Being on time is fine too. - As long as you're on time...
- Being on time is totally fine. - You could run late.
- Just make sure you're not. - Just make sure you're not.
I'm not saying you'll end up running late.
- Being on time is fine too. - All I'm saying...
(Shocked by the fact that the one with the loudest voice wins here)
- is that you could run late. - Unusual situations can pop up.
(A. You can show up at 9am.)
That's not it. If work begins at 9am,
- it's fine to show up at 9am. - Exactly.
If not, why not just tell people...
- to show up at 8:50am? - That's it!
- That's not the same thing. - She's right.
I'm having a hard time understanding this.
Guys, hold on.
(Then make it simple and say that work begins at 8:50am.)
You should say that office hours begin at nine instead.
- Office hours. - That it begins at nine.
Have you all worked part-time before?
- Of course. - Have you needed money before?
- Absolutely. - Of course.
When your boss said to show up at 9am,
(When you were a part-timer)
did you show up on the dot?
- Yes. - We're part-timers, so who cares?
- Even as part-timers? - Sure.
- When you're being paid? - You arrived on the dot...
and spent time getting changed?
Hye Jun just said something.
With a deep sigh,
she said, "When you're being paid?"
You can't act like this when you're an employee.
- That's because... - Someone else might be paying me,
- but it ends up as my money. - Hold on.
How is your boss supposed to run a business?
That's his problem, not mine.
(His answer leaves them speechless.)
- Hold on. - Because you can throw a punch...
(Goodness...)
- You're reacting out of emotion. - What was that?
- I'm not being emotional. - Knowing how to throw a punch...
- Let's go! - Be logical.
(Kim Thug debates like it's a physical showdown.)
- That's his problem, not ours. - This is a debate.
- Are you kidding me? - Who debates emotionally?
That's his problem, not mine.
(Going on)
You can't get emotional just because you lack logic.
(He's the most emotional one.)
Red means stop, and green means go.
People just follow the rules...
- as they're written. - Exactly.
- He's right. - That's true.
- Hold on. - That makes sense.
- You lost me. - He's right.
(Agreed.)
- Aren't I right? - Green means go.
(A. You can show up at 9am.)
- Of course. - Exactly. Green means go.
(They said 9am. What's with all the fuss?)
Are you going to jaywalk?
Let me make my point...
comparing this to soccer.
Jong Kook shows up early...
- so he can warm up. - Yes, to warm up.
To prevent injuries.
- Hey. - Exactly.
Doesn't the match begin at 10am?
(Retorter, the close associate, blows the whistle.)
- Yes, at ten. - When does he expect you to gather?
He compliments the members who get there...
- thirty minutes ahead of time. - The competence...
(Retorting)
He praises them.
When does he show up?
He's there 30 minutes ahead of time.
He warms up to prevent injuries.
(Emphasizing again)
- That's it. To prevent injuries. - To prevent injuries.
- I do that for me. - It's the same at the office.
(Retorting)
- It's the same thing. - That's for my sake.
- You need time to warm up. - It's the same at the office.
To stay efficient at work,
(B. You can't show up at 9am.)
you need to show up early and get everything set up.
(Coming to work early is like warming up.)
That's it. Your boss paid for your time starting at 9am.
Hye Jun said your boss paid for your time starting at 9am.
- That's it. - Exactly.
So why must we get there ten minutes early?
- Totally. - Are we getting paid extra?
- That's not it. From 9am... - Are we getting paid?
- That's why it's totally fine. - No, listen to me.
- That's right. - As long as we start work...
- No way. - at 9am on the dot, it's fine.
- He's right. - His payment covers your talent...
- starting from 9am. - Exactly!
So, you show up at 9am, turn on your computer,
- and go get coffee? - That's right.
- There you go. - Booting up your computer...
isn't what your boss is paying you for.
- That's it. - Nice!
- Good one, Hye Jun. - Then...
(Satisfied)
Hye Jun, there you go.
(A bonus for the exceptional employee)
- Thank you! - The office...
Booting up your computer...
Can't we just show up to work without playing mind games?
(That's so uptight.)
- Se Chan. - Yes?
Why is your shirt unbuttoned for a debate?
- I... - Button your shirt.
No, do as you want.
- Who cares? - Do as you want.
(Stripping)
Do whatever you want. There.
(My eyes!)
Do whatever you want.
- What... - I want to ask something.
(He shows off his pale tofu skin.)
- Do whatever you want. - What's wrong?
Aren't we allowed to wear whatever we want?
What do you think you're doing?
(An underboob office outfit that boosts workplace autonomy)
What? What's wrong with it?
- That's salacious. - If he's good at his job...
- If someone on my team... - What's his name again?
- Jong Kook. - Yes?
(Seok Sam has already forgotten Woo Min's name.)
- What's his name? - Stop talking to yourself.
- It's Yoo Myung. - Let us talk, will you?
- Yoo Myung? - Yes, Yoo Myung.
Hey, Yoo Myung.
- Who? - Yoo Myung?
- Who's Yoo Myung? - He's already famous, okay?
(Laughing)
I can't believe him.
- Are you kidding me? - What is it?
- This brat... - Did you tell him the wrong name?
(Flustered)
I can't believe him.
Who on earth is Yoo Myung?
(It's surprising that he actually believed it.)
- It's Woo Min. - Woo Min?
Hey, Woo Min.
- Yes? - Sorry about that.
(Laughing)
- He told me the wrong name. - Yoo Myung?
- Yes, I'm Yoo Myung. - Hear me out.
When did you get here today?
I made it here 30 minutes early.
(He arrived 30 minutes early.)
- See? - That's just...
- his personal choice. - It doesn't add up.
(You see?)
- Imagine... - Yes?
that your kid is sick.
You went to the clinic hoping to see the doctor,
- but the doctor walked in at 9am... - Playing the sympathy card.
(He starts the emotional appeal.)
right alongside you.
- Keep going. - He walks into his office,
boots up his computer, puts on his coat,
and drinks coffee,
- And goes to the bathroom. - all while your child is sick.
- That's it. - While your child is sitting sick.
(Nodding)
- That'd make you see red. - I rest my case.
(The emotional appeal strategy is starting to work.)
I know a lot of the staff members personally.
(Jong Kook counters the emotional appeal.)
Whenever we are scheduled to arrive around 10am,
I often ask when our camera crew will be there.
They usually reply with the exact time they'll be on set,
which is their official...
- call time. - Call time.
(There's no problem,)
Outside of that, it isn't considered part of their working hours.
(as long as they get their work done on time.)
A or B, please hold up your choice.
(The result of the heated debate)
- A or B, 1, 2, 3. - Okay, 1, 2, 3.
(What will the staff choose?)
- B. - It's B.
- It's close. - Neck and neck.
(The ratio is quite balanced.)
- It's a close one. - I see more Bs.
(Do you have to show up earlier?)
- There are more Bs. - I see more Bs.
- No, A wins. - I see more Bs.
(Or can you show up at 9am?)
I count 20 for B.
(B: No, 20 votes)
- I count 13. - For us?
(A: Yes, 13 votes, B: No, 20 votes)
The result is 20 to 13. B wins.
(B. "You can't show up at 9am" wins)
- B wins. - Of course.
- Nice one. - This is why Korea functions.
We still have a bright future.
- What a relief. - I know.
- I agree. B is right. - Of course.
- Exactly. Don't be a brat. - Absolutely.
(Team Jong Kook was actually for B.)
- You should get there early. - At least ten minutes early.
(His honest thoughts)
Consider how Korea became what it is today!
- Everyone worked hard. - Of course.
- We all got up early. - Get to places ahead of time.
(Team Jae Seok: 1, Team Jong Kook: 0)
- I hate showing up on the dot. - Don't be ridiculous.
We'll begin the second debate.
(The second debate topic)
This topic has been blowing up...
- on social media. - What is it?
What if your boss tripped and accidentally pulled your pants down?
What would you do first?
"Help the boss up first" versus "Pull up my pants first."
- My pants, of course! - My pants!
(Of course)
What are you talking about?
(Your boss tripped and accidentally pulled your pants down.)
Are you kidding me?
- Hold on. - What needs to be discussed?
(A. Help the boss up first. B. Pull up my pants first.)
- Pull up your pants first. - What is this?
(Chaos erupts over the unbalanced debate topic.)
- How is this a hot topic? - Pull up my pants first!
What the...
You could be gunning for a promotion.
(Full of ambition)
- Exactly. - Still.
- Let's hear her out. - What kind of debate is this?
Are we talking about a really high-level boss?
Do we still have our underwear on?
- Let's say it's the chairman. - Okay, it's the chairman.
So you work for Samsung, and Lee Jae Yong...
(They assume that it's the top executive with immense power.)
- Yes. - pulled your pants down.
Let's just say it's a chairman.
I've thought about it,
- and we should help the boss up. - Absolutely.
- While your pants are down? - That's fine.
(Employee Jee is blinded by power.)
- Exactly. - You still have your underwear on.
- How is that right? - That's just wrong.
(They are all leaning towards "Pull up my pants first.")
- Still... - It's about human dignity.
- Please... - What did you get?
You can help him up after pulling your pants up.
(B. Pull up my pants first.)
(Team Jong Kook got the easy B.)
- My pants? Good. - Yes, my pants.
- I'm so sorry. - If you think about it...
(A. Help the boss up first.)
- What did we get? - Answer A.
(Team Jae Seok got A.)
A, help the boss up first?
(It will be a tough debate for Team Jae Seok.)
Team Jae Seok supports A.
The boss should go first.
(How are they going to convince the staff members?)
Of course we should help the boss up first.
Your team is A, and your team is B.
(The second debate begins.)
We'll start the debate.
You go first.
(A. Help the boss up first.)
Do I matter at all?
- My underwear... - Who cares about my underwear?
It's between rationality and instinct.
- That's what we must consider. - Yes.
What is this? It's an opportunity that comes once in a lifetime.
- That's right. - To get promoted.
- You're right. - To become successful.
- Yes. - Actually...
- My underwear was exposed, - Yes.
- but ignore that. "Are you okay?" - "Boss!"
- "Are you okay?" - "Sir!"
That tone.
(Shaking his head)
- Where's your pride? - Then he'll say,
- "I'm sorry." - "Not at all!"
(It's your chance to win your boss over and set yourself for success.)
(I'm sorry.)
- "Not at all." - "Not at all."
Let's say your pants are down, and your underwear's exposed.
You're face-to-face with your boss.
Pretend someone took a photo of that.
Who would take a photo?
- Nowadays, for social media... - They would.
- It could get ten million views. - Yes.
(You could go viral as "Underwear Guy.")
"A touching true story."
- It'll become a moving story. - A moving anecdote.
- A moving... - A moving anecdote.
(Laughing)
Everyone would talk about it.
(The touching video could go viral,)
(and you might become the office hero.)
The boss's own child could leave a comment...
(Heartwarming True Story That Moved Office Workers to Tears)
that could be pinned to the top,
(Warning: You might cry)
(I'm the son of the man who fell in the video.)
- Yes. - making it famous.
(I remember my dad thanking him and getting teary-eyed that day.)
And also, let's pretend I was that boss.
- Yes. - I messed up like that.
- That's right. - I'd feel bad forever.
- You would. - Yes.
And that employee looked out for me before himself.
- Yes. - How grateful would you be?
(One day, he'll repay that kindness.)
- Very grateful. - I'd want to make up for it.
Seok Jin, let's say you're walking with Manager Yu.
Manager Yu fell and pulled down your pants.
Are you okay with that?
- Yes. - Yes. It's a rare happening.
Your son witnessed it.
(Seok Jin's son)
- That's fine. - I don't mind.
- Really? Your wife saw. - It's fine.
I'm in my underwear at home anyway.
- Oh, right. - It's no big deal.
I'm okay with that. It's an ordinary day.
(Hyun Woo won't be disappointed at all because it's not new.)
- I get it now. - That's just him.
Think about it this way.
You pull up your pants and don't get promoted.
There's no guarantee of a promotion.
If that meant a promotion, everyone would pull down your pants.
That kind of makes sense.
(The Gen Z employee is actually making sense today.)
- No? - Excuse me?
- What logic is that? - You made a huge leap.
That was a massive logical step.
The chairman happened to pull down my pants.
I don't know about much else, but if I were in that situation,
rather than use that to become successful,
I'd ask to be compensated since I suffered emotional damage.
- Yes. "Pay me!" - Yes.
- That's right. - That would be better.
(Instead of trying to butter up your boss for a promotion,)
- Chairman Lee Jae Yong... - You would do that.
(you'd have a better shot at getting compensated for emotional distress.)
- That's a better bet. - You...
I wouldn't want an employee like you.
(He's more the type to threaten people than suck up to them.)
That would be better. Then I'd switch jobs.
- Okay, switch jobs. - That would be better.
Yes. I'd save my pants.
Fine! Go to "2 Days 1 Night!"
Why would he do that?
Why would you say that?
(A sudden job switch announcement)
I won't go!
- Take your award and go. - I don't want to.
- You know the popular tagline. - Such as?
- "People come first." - So what?
Put the other person before...
- Aren't I a person too? - What?
Am I not a person because my pants are down?
- We're just dogs? - Yes.
(The debate sharks have found their target.)
- I know. - We just walk about like dogs?
- I'm someone's precious child. - We're dogs?
- I'm my mom's precious child. - Yes!
- We're precious too. - And...
- everyone saw my underwear. - That's right.
- I'd feel... - Yes.
I'd feel too ashamed to work here anymore.
- Yes. They saw my underwear! - It's okay.
(Crying)
Ye Eun, it's okay. Society won't let it lie.
- They'll help. - What if there were a hole?
- What if he tore a hole? - Yes.
Let's say Jong Kook is a singer who isn't well-known yet.
- I'm yet unknown. - And it's hard...
- to get a spot on "Inkigayo." - It is.
You're about to leave after a chat with the head of the variety team.
He pulled down your pants. You're known for your strong legs.
You'd want to show them off.
- You're proud of them. - You punk.
- Isn't that nonsense? - Also,
(Dumbfounded)
you sometimes wear underwear with a heart design on the back.
You sometimes do. You could turn it into a joke.
- A funny... - Has he lost his mind?
Do you have underwear with hearts?
- Who are they for? - He is out of control.
(But he doesn't deny it.)
- I'll stop right there. - That's your style.
(The only thing the debate revealed was his unexpected taste.)
- I like that. - I like it.
- The crew will take a vote. - Okay.
- One, - You'd save yourself.
- two, three. - It's about you.
Yes. Of course, that's right.
(An overwhelming number of people chose B.)
- B won. - There are more Bs obviously.
- B won. - Okay!
(Team Jong Kook wins.)
Great.
You must fend for yourself.
(B. Pull up my pants first.)
- You must dress yourself. - I think so too.
Pull up your pants first.
(Team Jae Seok: 1, Team Jong Kook: 1)
You're tied at one-one. Here's the final debate.
Okay.
(Can you date someone from the same company?)
Can you date someone from work?
(This means you can work and love at the same time,)
I want to go so bad so that I can see that face everyday.
(but should you risk the scary post-breakup aftermath?)
- You can date. - You can.
Yes, why not?
You can't stop love.
You can't hide love.
(These romantics are in favor of office romances.)
Lots of you dated at work.
I bet some of you dated colleagues in secret.
These people...
- Someone here married a colleague. - Yes.
(Some of them are a couple.)
Let's pick sides first.
(Many of them think it's okay.)
We must pick well.
(The key is which one you choose.)
We need to pick yes.
- One, two, three. - Pick well.
Yes, you must pick well.
What is it? Yes.
(B. No, you can't.)
- What? - It's no.
I got the no spoon.
Why were you pleased?
(Team Jong Kook got B.)
You were mistaken.
- You're an oddball. - I got it wrong.
I messed up.
(A. Yes, you can.)
Why is that bad?
- Why can't you? Explain. - I think...
(They already think they won.)
Jong Kook, why not?
Dating a colleague. That's okay.
(B. No, you can't.)
But not everyone gets a chance.
- What? - What does that mean?
(That's a wild argument.)
- Some get left out. - Yes.
(He points at someone.)
(What are you talking about?)
We should all give it up for those who can't date?
He feels deprived.
(Get rid of office romances that make everyone else feel left out.)
- A sense of deprivation. - Yes.
You dated someone here.
Who says I dated someone from the show?
Didn't you date an idol?
- Him? - Hang on.
- That's different. He... - Didn't you all date at work?
- Didn't you date a colleague? - I did.
- Didn't you? - I did. So what?
(Not ashamed)
(Employee Ha dated someone from the same company.)
- I dated a colleague. - You did.
Didn't you date someone from work?
Are you happy you dated at work?
Didn't you?
- What? - I know stuff. Did you or not?
- Spill. - I'm curious now!
- Yes or no? - Right now...
- Employee Ha. - I just...
(The debate battle turns into an expose.)
- Did you date a colleague or not? - Don't get worked up.
Don't get worked up.
(Oh, you're going there?)
Okay. Think about this, then.
- Listen. - Don't get worked up.
(They calm down and resume the debate.)
- I'll go into details. - Okay.
You dated someone at work, and everyone knew about it.
Then you broke up and dated someone else at work.
And you married this person.
- That afterthought... - Hang on.
(If you date coworkers back-to-back,)
In many ways...
(the memories of your past relationships can linger.)
Why do you assume you date multiple people at work?
We're talking about this one instance.
- I'm talking about the cons. - Yes.
- Dating at work... - I didn't mind.
- You were okay? - Yes.
- Haha, was it really okay? - Was it?
- Yes. - I see.
You told me it was uncomfortable.
- See? - Did you double-check or not?
(Did he have struggles that no one knew about?)
- Come on... - Did you or not?
(The shocking accusation from someone he trusted)
In real life, when you got caught...
- Did you double-check or not? - In real life.
- Oh, that? - Employee Ha.
- Do you remember? - Yes!
(Something must have come to mind.)
Leave me alone.
- Let's keep going! - Sit back down.
(He's out of control.)
- Sit down. - Okay!
- Employee Ha. - Fight me!
Sit down, Employee Ha.
- I'm right! - Oh, I'm so sorry.
- I'm sorry. - What the...
- Oh, dear. - Gosh.
Are you okay, sir?
- Get back up. - Oh, dear.
- Are you okay? - Are you?
- Are you all right? - I'm just fine.
(Your boss tripped and accidentally pulled your pants down.)
(A. Help the boss up first.)
Dating at work is fine if you keep it between yourselves,
(Crying)
(It negatively affects not only the people involved...)
- but because of that... - People around you.
(but also the company.)
- The company suffers. - And people mind.
If you date someone at work,
you want to go to work.
- Yes. - That's right.
- What if you argue? - What if you argue?
- Then you work harder. - What if you argue?
If you fight, you become determined to get promoted first.
- You work harder. - It helps.
- It's better for you. - "I'll get promoted before him."
(Office romances can improve work efficiency.)
You become less efficient if you break up.
- That's right. - That's why...
lots of companies forbid dating at work.
Why do you think you become less efficient...
at work if you date a colleague?
- Excuse me. - Yes?
You don't seem to know because...
you haven't dated many colleagues.
- What do you mean? - What? He met his wife at work!
(What did you say?)
- That was the only... - You two met at work!
(How can you say that to someone who married his coworker?)
- The one and only... - He dated at work!
(I saw it.)
- He dated! - Just that once.
(Not holding back)
- Did you see the rest? - Were you watching?
Did you?
You don't know his dating history!
- Did you see me date? - She was the only one.
That's why you don't get the cons!
I ended up marrying her.
- Yes. - I tied the knot.
That's why you don't get the cons!
- I'm saying there are pros to it. - Yes.
(I'm a success story of an office romance.)
We know that.
Lots of people on the Running Man team...
- That's right. - got married.
- Look at Ju Yong's face. - Yes.
- What's wrong? - He doesn't look happy.
(Producer Lee Ju Yong, married to the writer of Running Man)
- He looks so happy. - That guy.
There are times when he'd want to meet friends after work,
(After the shoot)
- That's right. - or do something else,
(You can't separate work from your personal life,)
but he never has the chance.
(so you have no time for yourself.)
Hey, Ju Yong! Are you happy or not? Yes or no, that's it.
- Yes, I'm happy. - See?
He sounds sad, though!
(He starts plotting against him.)
Are you for or against dating at work?
Well... I guess...
- It's okay, right? - Yes.
See?
- Be honest. - He said yes.
(His answer isn't quite clear.)
There's this inconvenience.
You can't give that kind of answer.
He was really honest.
- Let's vote. - Okay.
(The final vote)
- I wonder what Ju Yong will say. - On three.
- There's no stopping it. - We'll win.
(Office romance, A. Yes, you can. B. No, you can't.)
It shouldn't be banned.
- You can't make rules about love. - Right.
It would be funny if Ju Yong votes B.
Ju Yong...
(Which one will the staff members choose?)
- Okay, one... - One, two, three.
That's it. It's A.
(Many more voted A, that it's okay to date at work.)
Ju Yong voted B!
What?
(Did Producer Ju Yong choose B?)
- Ju Yong. - Ju Yong, you voted B?
Ju Yong, hold it up. Let's take a photo.
(Gathering evidence)
It worked out for me, but I saw many couples break up.
(Producer Ju Yong)
- Yes. - We won anyway.
Anyway, our team won.
(Team Jae Seok won 2:1.)
Team Jae Seok won.
Both teams can pick a random number...
(Both teams will randomly draw gold bars.)
- of gold bars. - Okay.
- The winning team will get more. - Okay.
(However, the winning team will get to draw more.)
As you check your envelopes,
name your favorite employee in the interview.
(After checking the gold bars,)
(they will vote for their favorite employee.)
My favorite employee?
The favorite employee will get two more gold bars.
(The one chosen as the favorite will earn 2 extra gold bars.)
You're voting for your favorite employee.
- It was Hye Jun. - Why?
(Hye Jun)
(During the debate)
She made a lot of good points in the debate.
I vote for Hye Jun.
(2 votes for Hye Jun)
Who is your least favorite employee?
It's Kim Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook)
He's oppressive, and within the hierarchy,
he causes a great deal of stress.
I vote for Ha Dong Hoon.
(The worst)
Overall, starting from his clothing, he was out of line.
(Haha)
Haha.
(Haha gets another vote as the least favorite employee.)
Why?
I didn't like him from the start of today's filming.
I vote for...
(He's the worst.)
They seem to care only about fending for themselves.
(Everyone followed their hearts and finished voting.)
I think the person only whined without any logic.
Hye Jun and Kang Hoon can sit there,
(They head to their next destination.)
- and I can sit here. - At the back?
- Sit in the back, Woo Min. - Okay.
- Hye Jun... - Putting your hair up...
- makes you look even thinner. - Really?
(Her new bun style is being praised.)
- That's called a bun, right? - Yes.
(Glancing)
Stop looking at me.
What's wrong with her?
- Stop looking at me, Se Chan! - Your bun...
(She's really enjoying the attention.)
- It doesn't look like a bun. - He keeps glancing at me.
I looked at it because it actually looks like poop.
Do you want your gums to collapse?
(Showing his gums)
She's...
Yes, I want collapsed gums. So what?
- The gum series is quite funny. - Yes.
She's got quite a few...
(She's been racking up memorable quotes about gums.)
- The teeth attack. - of those dental attacks.
I'll help you with those.
I'll go over there.
- Hurry up. - Hye Jun.
(Hoon gets on the bus.)
- Go to the very back. - Okay.
I shouldn't sit next to Ye Eun.
- I don't want to sit... - Let's move quickly.
- next to you either. - I'm not sitting there.
- Whatever. - You played me.
"You played me."
That sounded cool.
(By pretending he still has feelings,)
Right. Ye Eun should apologize...
(he reignites their old romance.)
- to Kang Hoon. - That's right.
You stole his heart...
I think he's a really charming person.
(I think Vata is a really charming person.)
The way he dances...
- Right, Vata. - Seriously.
So you were keeping an eye on all of that?
(Her old crush was watching from afar.)
- He kept track. - Goodness.
He was paying attention to that.
- He was keeping an eye on it. - He kept track.
I wanted to see what was so charming about him.
Why is he acting like that?
You should've treated me better when I was there.
"You should've treated me better when I was there."
- The tables have turned. - Ye Eun is a femme fatale.
(Fox Hoon's amazing acting makes her beam with a big smile.)
Ye Eun is amazing.
What were you going to do...
- if Kang Hoon really liked you? - I know, right?
That would have never happened.
(He gets his screen time and ends the skit right away.)
I'll tell you the results...
(The employee vote results are revealed.)
- of the favorite employee vote. - Okay.
- Starting with the least favorite. - Yes.
We voted for that as well.
The least favorite employee...
- received four votes. - Four votes.
(4 votes out of 10)
- Who is it? - The least favorite employee is...
Kim Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook, the least favorite employee)
- I knew it. - How come?
Kim Jong Kook.
- They voted for you. - Justice prevails!
- Justice prevails. - Okay.
(Not holding back)
- Justice prevails. - Justice prevails.
- Okay. - This is amazing.
(The 4 heroes came together to deliver justice.)
We didn't discuss it,
but I guess we were all thinking the same thing.
(When she asked the question,)
Who is your least favorite employee?
Kim Jong Kook.
(he answered immediately.)
The rule should be set.
(Yelling)
He gets too emotional...
during the debate.
(He was getting mad.)
He was getting worked up.
Jong Kook's attitude during the debate...
I felt like punching him.
He's so scary.
I feel like I was beaten up.
Someone said it felt like they had been beaten up.
(Hye Jun's opinion is revealed right away.)
That he was too aggressive.
(Looking at him nervously)
They all put their votes on you.
- I was too serious about it. - All Mighty.
(Jong Kook was chosen as the worst employee with 4 votes.)
- I was too serious about it. - They all voted for you.
You did get a little too angry.
I'll announce the favorite employee.
(The favorite employee is revealed.)
- The favorite employee. - The favorite employee...
- received three votes. - Three votes?
(3 votes out of 10)
(She got at least 2 votes.)
- It's Haha. - What?
(Haha, the favorite employee)
- Really? - What?
- It's Haha. - What?
(Haha, 3 votes)
- Really? - What?
I loved the scene where you took your pants off.
- That scene was nice. - Thank you.
(Seok Jin and Se Chan voted for him because his pants got pulled down.)
That scene was really nice.
- Nice. - You tried to impress the boss.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Haha, the favorite employee,
(Haha, the favorite employee, earns 2 gold bars.)
will get two additional gold bars.
I voted for you, Haha.
(Number of Gold Bars)
- I really voted for you. - Thank you so much.
(As the unexpected employee was voted the favorite...)
- Where are we? - We're now going to have...
the highlight of every office worker's day,
- which is lunch. - Okay!
We've prepared some of your favorite dishes.
Naengmyeon?
There's a sundaeguk restaurant,
That sounds amazing.
a Chinese restaurant,
- Nice. - Nice.
- and a BBQ restaurant. - BBQ?
- Let's go to the BBQ restaurant! - BBQ restaurant!
- Protein. - Let's go to the BBQ restaurant!
- BBQ restaurant! - You can have naengmyeon too.
- They're all so nice. - Let's go to the BBQ restaurant.
- They definitely have it. - All BBQ restaurants have it.
(All BBQ restaurants have naengmyeon.)
- Everyone will pick that one. - Each restaurant...
- has its own conditions for dining. - Yes.
If you successfully gather according to the conditions,
you'll be able to eat at that restaurant.
- So there are conditions. - If you fail,
- you'll only get rice and kimchi. - Goodness.
- Then Kang Hoon won't get to eat. - Kang Hoon...
- He'll only have rice. - He can't eat kimchi.
(Hoon, who doesn't eat kimchi, will just eat rice.)
- What are the conditions? - I'll tell you the conditions.
For the first restaurant,
you succeed if an odd number of people gather.
- Goodness. - Right.
For the second restaurant,
you succeed if the combined ages of the people gathered...
is between 120 and 150.
- I should go to that one. - Seok Sam should go there.
- Seok Sam, Jong Kook, and me. - Even if just the two of us go...
(The older guys)
- Yes. - That would meet the condition.
For the third restaurant,
you succeed if the number of men and women is equal.
- In pairs. - In pairs.
(A maximum of 3 pairs can be matched.)
- Like couples. - There are three women.
Each restaurant has 30 gold bars at stake.
So the people who succeed...
can split the gold bars equally among themselves.
That means the fewer the people, the better.
(That means the fewer people in the restaurant, the better.)
It would be amazing if two couples get them.
(The fewer people there are, the more gold bars you get.)
We'll have to move in secret.
You can move freely between the restaurants...
within the time limit,
but if you fail to enter a restaurant in time, you fail.
(If you're still outside when the time runs out, you fail.)
- Okay. - Within the time limit?
(BBQ restaurant, sundaeguk restaurant, Chinese restaurant)
You could fail while you're out on the street.
(The three restaurants are quite far apart by car.)
This is crazy.
We'll give you badges with your age...
(They'll hand out badges showing their ages.)
as of the filming date.
You can add up the ages shown on the badges.
- Did you really have to write... - Then...
- our ages here? - Fifty-three.
- Did you have to write them here? - I'm still in my 30s.
(Seok Jin, who is 60, doesn't really like the idea.)
You're being too much.
How old does it say you are?
- Sixty. - Sixty.
We gave you the one that makes you look the youngest.
Seriously.
- My birthday hasn't passed yet. - We're agemates.
- I'm joking. - Your birthday hasn't passed yet?
(Someone born in 1995 whose birthday has passed)
- What? - What happened?
(Someone born in 1994 whose birthday hasn't passed yet)
- My birthday passed. - It passed?
(Both of them are 31.)
- Your birthday passed. - Mine hasn't passed yet.
- You're the same age? - Yes.
(Pretending to be close)
We're friends.
- Hye Jun. - That's what you'll go with?
You'll each be provided with a car.
(They'll travel separately in their own vehicles.)
- Okay. - Head to the restaurant you want.
What do you want to eat, Hye Jun?
- Me? Should I be honest? - Is it meat?
- No. - What do you want to eat?
Chinese food.
- I was thinking of that too. - Chinese food?
Chinese naengmyeon also tastes good.
There's Chinese naengmyeon too.
- Chinese naengmyeon tastes good. - Chinese naengmyeon tastes good.
(Perfect teamwork)
- Chinese naengmyeon tastes good. - Should I have Chinese naengmyeon?
But we don't know what the condition is...
- We don't know. - We have to go around and check.
I'll get going now.
- Okay. - First...
We don't know anything yet.
(The 30-minute countdown begins.)
- What should I eat? - There's no use planning it here.
There's a grasshopper!
Jae Seok!
It's been a while since I saw a grasshopper.
(Jae Seok chose the wrong car.)
Go somewhere else. We have to go somewhere.
We have to get going. Go away.
Quickly get off the car.
You have to live here, Jae Seok.
Get off the car.
(Anxious)
I just found a grasshopper.
It will lose its family if it comes with us.
We have to get going, Jae Seok.
(Go back to your family, Jae Seok.)
Grasshopper!
It got off, right? Good.
That's a relief.
You should live with your family.
(He gets in the car after sending Ttuk away.)
I'll go to the BBQ restaurant first.
I'll go to the BBQ restaurant.
I'll definitely have naengmyeon at the BBQ restaurant.
Naengmyeon at the BBQ restaurant.
Let's get going first.
(Meanwhile, the real Jae Seok is...)
I think I'll have to see.
I'll first go to the sundaeguk restaurant.
- Sundaeguk. Yes. - To the sundaeguk restaurant.
We might not get to eat.
(He'll go there first and check what it takes to succeed.)
Lunch...
Couldn't you just let us eat?
(He's sensitive because he hasn't eaten anything.)
Why do you always...
Why do you feed us like this?
Haha will go to the sundaeguk restaurant.
(Jae Seok's prediction)
I'm craving Chinese food too.
(What is Old Haha, who likes gukbap, doing?)
I'll first check out the BBQ restaurant.
(Unlike what Jae Seok thought, he's going to the BBQ restaurant.)
The BBQ restaurant will probably be popular.
Let's check out the condition there.
Let's check out the mission.
Let's see what the condition is.
(What does it take to complete the mission at the popular place?)
I should go to all the restaurants to know the conditions.
Are we here? We're here.
(Haha arrives at the BBQ restaurant.)
Goodness. Look who's here.
Hold on. Don't get out yet.
(Someone is already here.)
Woo Min.
(It's Woo Min.)
- What's the mission here? - To come in pairs.
(What are the conditions for completing the mission?)
(Man-woman couples)
- Man-woman couples. - Man-woman couples.
(BBQ restaurant: Man-woman couples)
Man-woman couples.
(The female members have to show up for the mission to succeed.)
- Are you the only one here? - Yes.
- I'll check the other restaurants. - If only one...
(Man-woman couples)
- Go ahead. - Okay.
(Without hesitation)
(Woo Min will stay at the BBQ restaurant.)
I could have a big advantage there.
People are gathering here.
There are two vans here, right?
We have to go around to all the restaurants.
(Two cars are coming.)
Please let it be a woman.
If just one woman gets out...
(Will the men and women be able to pair up?)
Why aren't they getting out?
Isn't that one of the members' vans?
(He's nervous.)
Wait. You can see it from here.
(Mr. Jee is testing the waters.)
Man-woman...
You need to come as a man-woman couple.
I should give Ji Hyo a call.
(Woo Min bravely approaches the van.)
(He's suddenly very enthusiastic.)
- Seok Jin. - Yes?
(He's talking with Ji Hyo.)
- How many people went there? - Did you arrive?
What's the condition there?
I haven't...
A grasshopper!
- I haven't... - A grasshopper!
A grasshopper! There's a grasshopper!
(He said goodbye earlier. Why is he here?)
The grasshopper came inside.
It's the grasshopper from earlier.
It will lose its family if it comes with us.
(He thought he had left the grasshopper behind,)
(but Jae Seok clung to his butt and came with him!)
- Should I sit here? - Yes, that's right.
It's the grasshopper from earlier. See?
I told you to get out of the car earlier.
You should have gotten out of the car there.
You don't feel like a stranger, Grasshopper.
I gave you advice because you didn't feel like a stranger.
(Upset)
Why did you get in the car with us?
You're talking about a real grasshopper,
- not our Grasshopper? - It's not our Grasshopper.
It's a real grasshopper.
I feel bad for the grasshopper.
(Stuck to Seok Sam like glue)
I should drop it later.
Okay.
(Woo Min spotted Seok Sam and Grasshopper.)
(Is there a female member in this van?)
I can't see anything here.
(It's not a woman again.)
(Hoon was hiding in cover for no reason.)
Why isn't he entering?
I should check.
(He gets out first.)
- Woo Min. - Hoon.
Are you the only one here?
(There are 4 men at the BBQ restaurant.)
- I'm the only one here. - Really?
Why didn't more come to the BBQ place?
(Hoon checked the mission as well.)
- I know, right? - If we go in...
We have to enter in man-woman couples here.
(That's the requirement.)
- But it's just you and me. - Exactly.
- There's Seok Jin as well. - Seok Jin is here too?
(Oh, right.)
- Guys! - Seok Jin!
- You'll fail if you just stay here. - We can't go in here.
We have to enter in man-woman couples here.
I saw it from a distance. Isn't that the condition?
You should just leave, then.
What about you?
I'll stay here for a bit.
You should leave.
- Where should I go? - If the three of us stay here...
We have three female guests today.
All three of them have to come here for us to enter.
That's true.
(The old man shows up last and kicks everyone else out.)
It's impossible to eat from here.
You have the lowest chance...
of succeeding here.
- Then I'll... - Are you going to leave?
(Hoon leaves for now.)
- check out the other restaurants. - Okay.
(Yoo Myung and Seok Sam are left.)
We need two female members to come here.
- That's right. - Right?
(Where is Hye Jun, a female guest, going?)
We're here.
Goodness. I guess I'm the only one here!
Thank you.
(Which restaurant did Hye Jun come to?)
(She chose the Chinese restaurant, as she mentioned earlier.)
(What's the condition for the Chinese restaurant?)
(Odd number)
Can I go in?
Oh no.
We need an odd number of people present.
(Chinese restaurant: Odd number)
(Sundaeguk restaurant: Combined age of 120 to 150)
It'll be game over if someone joins me.
I don't think anyone will come though.
Am I the only one here?
(No one's here!)
What if...
no one else comes?
Do I really get to keep all 30 gold bars?
(Wishing as hard and fast as possible)
It'll be an odd number of people.
(Rattling)
(Her wishes come to a sudden halt.)
(She gets all the gold if she's the only one here.)
(Someone's here.)
Someone's here.
(Her dream is crushed in just 3 seconds.)
(Sighing)
(Hello!)
Oh dear.
(Yang Ssaebssaeb enters the Chinese restaurant.)
What happened?
I was hoping to get all the gold.
(Chinese restaurant: Odd number)
Well, in your dreams.
(Now that there are 2 people, the number is even.)
We need an odd headcount.
Yes. Either one more person joins us,
or you have to leave.
Am I the one who has to leave?
I won't be able to accept that deal.
(Brazen)
What do you want to have?
Me? Chinese naengmyeon.
- They don't have that? - Hey, they have mul naengmyeon.
Odd-number naengmyeon! Wait, that didn't make sense.
(Barging in)
Odd number naengmyeon! Wait, that didn't make sense.
(One more odd-number naengmyeon!)
- What does that even mean? - An odd number...
- I meant we're an odd number. - Okay, we're good.
(Chinese restaurant: Odd number)
It's just the three of us. I thought you wanted barbecue.
(Including Ye Eun, it's an odd number again.)
I came here thinking more people would go there.
They have mul naengmyeon.
- No Chinese naengmyeon though. - I'm good with mul naengmyeon.
(The Naengmyeon Sisters are reunited.)
Please. Let it end with just us.
I was by myself at first,
- so I thought I was getting... - Really?
(Sad)
all 30 gold bars.
Hold on. This means we'll get ten gold bars each.
Ten gold bars are a good bargain.
(What?)
- Exactly. - I could go somewhere else...
(Tiger Moth isn't content with 10 gold bars.)
and get all 30 bars.
- You couldn't. - Or get 15.
- Think about it. - There are three of us here,
so the other restaurants must have higher numbers.
- I should just go. - Why?
(He refuses to hear.)
- What are you doing? - That means...
we won't get any gold bars.
- Se Chan, please. - What?
(If Se Chan leaves, it becomes an even number again.)
Why are you making me stay?
- My donkey. - Your what?
What? What are you talking about?
(Coming up with his nickname in a rush)
- My donkey! - Since when am I your donkey?
(Tadpole and Donkey are being unnecessarily dramatic.)
- Tadpole, what is this? - My donkey, please.
Do I look like a donkey?
Because of your receding gums.
My what?
- Because of your receding gums. - My what?
(They look alike!)
Ye Eun wants to crush them herself, not that they're crushed already.
- Really? - Se Chan, please.
- Hold on a second. I hear you. - You can't go.
(Donkey is offended.)
Hold on. How long do we have?
You still have a lot of time left.
- I'll just see how things are. - What do you mean?
- I should see how things are. - If that's the case,
why don't you go with Ye Eun?
Why don't you go with Ye Eun?
She'll get all the gold.
(Laughing)
- I'll just go. - Then...
I'm going with you, then.
Then Hye Jun will get all the gold bars.
You know what I'm saying, right?
(I want both of you to leave.)
It's better that way.
Anyway, I'm leaving. You two stay here.
I'm better off leaving.
(Ssaebssaeb leaves in search of a bigger payout.)
(Okay.)
(What about Ye Eun?)
What do I do?
(Staying and leaving will both hurt her.)
(Will it become an odd number again?)
Should I get Ji Hyo over here?
- What? - I can ask Ji Hyo over here.
I should check...
(Jae Seok is at the sundaeguk restaurant.)
- the conditions first. - Sure.
Is this the place where our ages need to add up to 120 to 150?
(Sundaeguk restaurant: Combined age of 120 to 150)
(Since Jae Seok is 53, he needs another 67 to 97 years.)
Seok Sam has to be here.
Wait. Someone's here. Who is it?
(Right then, 2 cars have arrived at the same time.)
Who's here?
We can get three people who add up to over 120.
Who is it?
(Ji Hyo is here.)
- Hey, Ji Hyo. - Jae Seok.
- I thought... - Who's this?
Why on earth are you here?
(Jong Kook also arrives at the sundaeguk restaurant.)
Why else? Hold on.
We're 50, 53...
- That's 103. - I'm 50.
- Perfect. - Really?
We fit right in that range.
(Since 147 falls between 120 and 150, it qualifies!)
- No way. - We fit right under 150.
We can block anyone who tries to join us.
You know what's great? They serve a summer dish.
- I saw that. - Would you look at that?
(The conditions are met, and it has everything they need!)
We can all get what we want.
- There's clear beef bone soup. - There's everything.
- Wait. - Someone else is here.
- Someone's coming? - Who is it?
(Just as things are getting good, a car approaches.)
- Who is it? - I think it's Haha.
- Just don't. - Are you kidding me?
(They're doomed unless this person is 3 years old.)
- Who is it? Just leave. - Unbelievable.
Who is it? Let's see.
(Don't stop and keep going.)
(Which clueless uninvited guest just joined them?)
Who's in the van?
- Hoon, are you kidding me? - Darn.
(35-year-old Kang Hoon)
- Just leave already. - That weasel.
- Just go. - Go away already.
- Leave. - What?
But over there...
- Just leave already. - The BBQ restaurant...
- requires man-woman couples, - Leave!
(He was already kicked out of the BBQ restaurant.)
and only Seok Jin and Woo Min were there.
- Really? - Yes.
You push the total over 150.
(It's 182 in total.)
- Exactly. - We can't have you here.
Go to the other restaurant.
- Exactly. - The Chinese restaurant.
But I don't want to have Chinese food.
You didn't mention sundaeguk earlier.
- Why did you come here? - They serve kimchi here.
Exactly.
(The 147 trio is attacking him with kimchi.)
- What, then? - I don't want Chinese food.
- Come on. - They don't serve kimchi...
- with Chinese food. - Just go.
- Where's the Chinese restaurant? - Why do I have to leave?
- We were here first. - We already fit the requirement.
(Gatekeeping)
Where's the Chinese restaurant?
I haven't made it over there yet.
See how things are there.
I don't mind Chinese food.
- Maybe I should go there. - Why not?
I'm craving Chinese right now.
Why would you leave when we fit the requirement?
(He doesn't understand.)
Because Hoon joined us!
(The jjamppong lover is ruining the game.)
- What if someone else comes? - Let's count first.
How old... Wait, you're 35.
Don't we fit the requirement too?
(It's 129 in total, which meets the requirement.)
We meet the requirement. It's over 120, right?
- Adding 95 to... - You're over 120.
- It works. - It still works.
Get lost then.
Get lost and don't come back.
I'll see how things are...
- at the Chinese restaurant. - Just go.
This is great. Nice one, Hoon.
(Will it stay as 129?)
- We make a good group. - Right.
- I like this trio. - We're in the safe zone.
I like playing it safe.
He's not picking up.
(It's still an even number at the Chinese restaurant.)
Please let one more person be here.
(Chinese restaurant: Odd number)
Well...
Maybe you should go.
Hye Jun, really?
If you leave...
(Hye Jun doesn't give up.)
I can share the gold I earn.
(If you leave, I can share the gold I earn.)
- How many would I get? - I can give you some of it.
(Tempted)
You'll get 30 gold bars if you end up here alone.
- Yes, 30 gold bars. - I want at least 10 of them.
Of course!
(She's so easy to persuade.)
- Of course you'll get that much. - Really?
I even thought about asking for 13 gold bars.
Let's say I ended up here alone and got all 30 gold bars,
(They reached a deal where she gets to take all the gold bars.)
- I'll give you 11 of them. - Really? Okay.
(The deal is made, but Haha walks in.)
Wait, is this the Chinese restaurant?
I mean...
(Awkward)
Why don't we go somewhere else?
(They need to kick Haha out for their plan to work.)
(Someone is calling Hye Jun.)
- Hello? - No one's here.
Woo Min, where are you?
The BBQ restaurant. What about you?
You should come to the naengmyeon place.
The BBQ restaurant requires mixed-gender couples.
All this place needs is one female member.
Does that mean there are four of you there?
No, it'll just be me and you.
Really?
(Okay!)
- Just get here right away. - Got it.
Please. You have to come here right now.
Okay, fine.
(While Hye Jun thinks of running,)
- Are you with there with Hye Jun? - Yes.
(Ddochi is talking with Seok Sam.)
Aren't you in the mood for barbecue?
We can feast on meat...
if you come here with Hye Jun.
- Naengmyeon too. - Got it.
(He's also telling her to come to the BBQ restaurant.)
They also have cold kimchi noodles. What will it be?
Say "apple" if you'll be here and say "strawberry" if not.
Apple.
Got it. I'll wait for you.
(They agree to meet at the BBQ place too.)
- Who's coming here? - Woo Min.
- Woo Min's coming here? - Yes.
But he's at the BBQ restaurant.
I know, but he said...
He must be here.
Really? Are you leaving?
No, I'm going outside to show him where we are.
(Awkward)
Really?
(Glancing)
- To show him the way. - I see.
If Woo Min joins us,
(It's strange.)
- we'll have an even number. - Hye Jun, is he coming here?
Yes, he's coming here.
Where is he?
I'll bring him here.
(Laughing awkwardly)
- What's going on? - Ye Eun...
Where is he?
Where's Woo Min?
(They leave awkwardly.)
Woo Min!
What? Then that just leaves me.
(Haha lucked out without having to do anything.)
Woo Min!
Hye Jun, are you going to the BBQ restaurant?
I heard we'd meet the requirement if we go there.
How did you know that?
Seok Jin called.
(There won't be two people then.)
Mixed-gender couples at the BBQ restaurant.
We'll meet at the BBQ restaurant.
- Got it. - The BBQ restaurant.
(They each get in their own cars.)
- We have to be there. - Sure.
(She notifies Seok Sam right away.)
- Seok Jin. - Hey.
I'm headed to the BBQ restaurant with Hye Jun.
Okay, got it.
Can you take me to the sundaeguk restaurant?
The sundaeguk restaurant?
(Hye Jun heads to the sundaeguk restaurant instead.)
I'm heading over now. I'll be there in four minutes.
(BBQ restaurant: Man-woman couples)
All we need is you guys.
- Then... - We'll be a group of four.
(Sundaeguk restaurant: Combined age of 120 to 150)
They won't hit the requirement if Ye Eun goes alone.
(She thinks she has a better chance at the sundaeguk restaurant.)
So I'm headed to the sundaeguk restaurant.
It'll be a done deal once you get here.
Got it, sis. Sis?
Just get here.
(Sundaeguk restaurant: Combined age of 120 to 150)
I hope this brings back memories.
Sillim-dong had the best sundaeguk.
- That's true. - Anyang had good restaurants too.
(Peeking)
Who's there?
(Hye Jun, age 31, arrives at the restaurant.)
- Get in here first. - Come on over...
(Hye Jun: 31, Hoon: 35, Ji Hyo: 44, Jong Kook: 50)
- and talk to us a bit. - Join us for now.
(Total: 160)
- Why did you suddenly come here? - What?
Our combined age already meets the requirement.
They're being really territorial.
(The 39-year-old Se Chan also joins them.)
- No way. - They're being really territorial.
No way.
Why are you suddenly here? Come in and explain.
(Se Chan: 39, Hye Jun: 31, Hoon: 35, Ji Hyo: 44, Jong Kook: 50)
(Total: 191)
Just go to the BBQ restaurant together.
No way. You should stay, Se Chan.
- What about you guys? - We're a done deal here.
(With just the 3 of them, it's 129, which is safe.)
Do you know what the issue is?
The BBQ restaurant...
and Chinese restaurant are too far away.
(Their combined age exceeds the requirement.)
- What? - We could run out of time.
- I'm here. - Hurry up, will you?
(Ddochi arrives at the BBQ restaurant.)
Where's Hye Jun?
- Why isn't Hye Jun here? - Hye Jun...
She left the Chinese restaurant before me.
(BBQ restaurant: Man-woman couples)
- Okay. - Hi.
- Are we a group of four? - Yes.
It'll be four of us when Hye Jun gets here.
What if someone else comes here?
(They need one more woman to meet the condition.)
We should throw them out by force if we must.
Who's at the BBQ restaurant?
(Sundaeguk restaurant: Combined age of 120 to 150)
At the BBQ restaurant?
- Ye Eun and... - Ye Eun.
(Buzzing)
- And? - And Woo Min.
- Woo Min. - Hey, Woo Min.
Where is he?
- Where are you? - I'm on my way.
(Lying)
Let’s go if Ye Eun made it there.
I got a feeling you weren't coming,
- so I called. Are you sure? - Let's get going.
Yes, I'm on my way.
(Acting)
- Aren't we almost there? - She's blocking the door.
I'm two minutes out.
(Hye Jun is acting like Ssaebssaeb would.)
- Okay, get here fast. - Sure.
(After Woo Min ends his call)
Unbelievable.
- Do you want to team up? - What?
If Hye Jun doesn't come here...
(Woo Min tries to pair up with Ye Eun, just in case.)
- Is Hye Jun not coming? - I'm not sure.
She said she was two minutes out.
She left before I did.
Want to team up with me if she doesn't show up?
(Whispering)
Hold on.
(Meanwhile, Jae Seok arrives at the Chinese restaurant.)
(Chinese restaurant: Odd number)
Don't tell me everyone's hiding.
(It becomes an even number with 2 people.)
Where were you?
- The sundaeguk place? - The sundaeguk restaurant.
So what will it be?
- What? - Are you going to stay here?
Yes, I'm staying.
(Jae Seok isn't going to budge.)
- Manager Yu. - What?
I want to take you down.
- What? - I want you to starve.
Then stay here.
(Acting tough)
(Pathetic psychological warfare)
- You're fighting back? - Yes.
- Okay, then. - Okay, fine.
It looks like you think you have things under control.
(Taking out his phone)
(Haha calls someone.)
- Who are you calling? - Why ask?
You're urgently calling...
- Hye Jun's coming? - Are you sure?
(Vibrating)
- She said she's coming. - She's coming?
(Ye Eun doesn't answer the call.)
I don't think you can eat here.
- It's not just me. It's you too. - The person cannot pick up.
Why won't they pick up? This is getting insane.
- Why... - Are you calling Ye Eun?
(Quick-witted)
What...
(Haha gets up.)
- Enjoy your meal. - Goodbye.
(I won.)
(Chinese restaurant: Odd number)
(There's 1 person, so it's an odd number.)
I should call Seok Sam just in case.
Ye Eun doesn't trust me.
(Haha leaves.)
Where is Seok Sam?
- Hey, Jae Seok. - Where are you?
(BBQ restaurant: Man-woman couples)
I'm at the BBQ restaurant.
Why are you there when you can't get the numbers right?
(Chinese restaurant: Odd number)
- Where are you? - At the Chinese restaurant.
How many are there?
Right now it's just me, I think.
- For real? - But I think...
someone will come in.
(Tempted)
- Definitely. And it'll become two. - Yes.
I'll make it three... Okay. I get what you're saying.
I got it. Okay. I understand.
(Seok Sam is persuaded.)
Hey. I think Hye Jun went somewhere else.
You two can eat here.
- Where will you go? - Stay here and eat.
(BBQ restaurant: Man-woman couples)
I'll go to the Chinese place. You eat here.
I don't think Hye Jun will come. We all go down if I stay.
- Okay. Let's eat. - Okay?
(Ye Eun and Woo Min will stay. Seok Sam will leave.)
- Stay and eat. Good luck. - We'll stay.
- Good luck. Let's eat! - Good luck.
- Let's eat. Let's! - Let's eat. Eat!
- Let's eat! - Eat!
Let's get going. I don't think Hye Jun will come.
(Seok Jin switches to Chinese.)
I can't even reach... The Chinese restaurant, please.
(Chinese restaurant: Odd number)
(Jae Seok's calling someone else.)
Where are you, Ssaebssaeb?
I'm at the hangover... The sundaeguk restaurant.
(Sundaeguk restaurant: Combined age of 120 to 150)
Where are you?
(Jae Seok doesn't know how things will turn out,)
- At the Chinese restaurant. - You're alone, aren't you?
(so he's considering multiple options.)
I'm alone right now, but something will happen at the last minute.
I'll come over, then.
- Yes. Come here right away. - Okay. Will do.
I'll get random people to come here.
- One more... - Okay. Will do.
(He told Se Chan to come to the Chinese restaurant.)
It's Jong Kook, though.
- What will you do, Hoon? - Hang on.
What will you do?
- I don't know. - Don't talk without me.
- Okay. - I'm hurt.
- Okay. Let's all talk. - I hate feeling left out.
- I'll leave. - No, Hye Jun, you stay.
- They just need you. - You can eat.
(Sundaeguk restaurant: Combined age of 120 to 150)
- Look at those eyeballs. - Those eyes...
(Hye Jun, Ji Hyo, and Jong Kook's ages add up to 125.)
Those eyeballs...
They're looking at us closely.
- Stay. - We'll help so you can eat.
(Hye Jun is going to stay at the sundaeguk restaurant.)
(BBQ restaurant: Man-woman couples)
It's perfect. We each get 15 gold bars.
(The conditions are met here.)
We score big.
(If they can hold out for just 9 more minutes,)
- Please let it be just us. - Please.
(they can split the gold bars and take 15 each.)
(Phone vibrating)
Hello?
- Ji Ye Eun. - Yes?
(Be quiet.)
Shall we do something cool as the Free Meal Couple?
For real? What's that?
(BBQ restaurant: Man-woman couples)
- You're at the BBQ place? - Yes.
Who else is there? There's a guy and two girls, right?
No. There's one guy and one girl.
You're with Woo Min.
Yes.
- Join me instead. - What?
(He smugly suggests that they form a duo.)
- Then... - That's crazy.
Pretend you're leaving and hide in the kitchen.
I'll walk proudly into the BBQ restaurant.
Don't come here.
I'm coming.
Then bring another woman.
No, I can't stand how cheeky you're being.
(When she turned down his brilliant strategy, he got bitter.)
You say we're a team...
Seok Jin left.
I'll... I don't care, then.
Don't come here.
The BBQ place, please.
- No way. - Do as I say or you don't eat.
(Haha is coming.)
This is insane. Call Hye Jun quick.
(He calls Hye Jun right away.)
- She's not picking up? - No.
- Really? - Won't someone come?
(Phone vibrating)
Woo Min keeps calling.
He wants you to join him?
(Sundaeguk restaurant: Combined age of 120 to 150)
If you go, that makes four.
- It's better to stay here. - It is.
(Hye Jun doesn't answer his call because she's likely to succeed.)
Right? If you count the gold bars you'll get.
I'll call Ji Hyo.
(Switching their target to Ji Hyo)
- Hi. - Where are you?
Are you at the BBQ place?
- Haha's on his way here. - Okay.
If you come, we have the right number.
(If you come, we have the right number!)
The Chinese restaurant?
- Really? - That's the couple place?
- The Chinese restaurant? - Really?
Yes. If Haha comes and you come too, we have the exact number.
(It's Hye Jun's voice!)
Hurry. Run away and join us.
- Okay. I'll... - Ji Hyo.
(Is he acting cute?)
I want to eat. Come quick.
- Run out of there. - Okay.
(The combination of cuteness and obsession)
- Okay, okay. Bye. - Bye.
Hye Jun's there with her.
(She's just realized.)
He's here.
(BBQ restaurant: Man-woman couples)
Leave.
(Haha enters.)
What's this? Is this a date?
We're filming our own dating show.
What a joke. Are you on a rebound?
- A dating show. - Okay. I'm here.
- Your numbers are off. - No.
- How so? - Do you know why?
(Mocking)
Ji Hyo's coming.
You... Give me just 30 seconds. Come with me.
(He urgently asks to talk to her, who's acting up today.)
Sorry. Excuse us.
Ye Eun, I really...
(Please don't abandon me.)
- Okay. Just 30 seconds. - I know. I'm good at...
He's my younger brother's age.
Come here.
(Woo Min is left alone.)
I like Woo Min too.
Listen.
(They begin a 1-on-1 conversation.)
- Do as I say if you're convinced. - Okay.
- The gold bars. - Yes.
We could get 15 of them.
How exactly?
Get in the car and drive it around to the back of the kitchen.
(Peekaboo)
- What about Woo Min? - Woo Min, wait. We're talking.
(Pretending)
- It's too cold inside. - Okay.
- And then... - Yes.
(He follows them outside.)
He'll... Come here.
Woo Min. Will you excuse us?
- What? - We won't run away.
I know you won't.
And then...
(Whispering)
(Almost shouting)
Run out through the kitchen?
I should escape out the kitchen?
(Ddochi refuses to cooperate again.)
I didn't think you'd be like this.
No, Woo Min.
- It's not like that. - I'm hurt.
- You're Busan buddies. - Woo Min.
(Woo Min realized how disloyal Haha was.)
- I'll leave and not eat. - No, Woo Min.
- I don't mean... Woo Min. - As the younger guy,
(Eat a lot.)
- I'll leave so you can eat. - No, it's not like that.
- I'll skip lunch. - Woo Min, it's not that.
(His Busan buddy is hurt.)
- You're wrong. - It's fine.
(He plays a Lotte baseball team theme song.)
(A cheap trick to appease his Busan buddy)
(It's working!)
The strongest, Lotte Giants
(They form the BBQ alliance over an emotional anthem.)
She won't pick up.
(Phone buzzing)
Is someone coming?
(Sundaeguk restaurant: Combined age of 120 to 150)
(Ji Hyo looks outside.)
There are four at the BBQ place. It's better to stay here.
(Scratching)
You're standing by the door weighing your options.
Ji Hyo, consider the math. There are four people there.
(Ji Hyo, please. You should hurry up.)
(You said you wanted to have meat!)
You get more gold if you stay with us.
(Ye Eun is trying to persuade her through text messages.)
Here's what I'll do. If Ji Hyo...
goes to the BBQ place or Hye Jun goes somewhere,
I'm coming too.
To kill you. Most definitely.
We need you here now.
(Kim Viper throws out a warning.)
If you betray our perfect team, I have to punish you.
I can't go down alone.
- Five minutes to go. - I'm scared.
(There are 5 minutes left!)
I'll blow it all up.
(Will Ji Hyo be able to escape this place?)
Come here soon.
(Chinese restaurant: Odd number)
I hope I get to eat.
(Jae Seok's alone, which is an odd number.)
I could eat on my own.
- Ssaebssaeb's here. - Please.
- I don't need just him. - Please.
(Se Chan, who loves Chinese food, is here.)
This is bad.
(Chinese restaurant: Odd number)
- I need you here now. - I'm on the way.
(There are 2 people now, so it's an even number.)
- How many are there? - I swear I'm coming.
You and me make an even number.
- Seok Sam's on the way. - Seok Jin? Okay.
(Fortunately)
Jae Seok wants me, so I make it an odd number.
(Meanwhile, Seok Sam is heading to the Chinese restaurant.)
(BBQ restaurant: Man-woman couples)
You are a team.
(People at the BBQ restaurant believes that Ji Hyo is coming.)
Ji Hyo's coming, though.
- Let me go. - Come on...
(Haha wants to leave because Ye Eun annoys him.)
- Don't cling to me. - Take a seat.
Why are you like this? What are you doing?
(Woo Min and Ye Eun are completely blocking him.)
There you go.
- I'm going to the toilet. - The toilet?
I'll come with you.
It's fine. I have a brother.
What?
(She'd follow him to the ends of the earth if she had to.)
- Let's go. - I mean...
- I'm going to the toilet. - Pee right here.
(Is she speaking in a dialect?)
Give him an empty bottle.
(Actually checking the bottle)
(Woo Min, she has you under control.)
She has you under control.
(Laughing)
That was fun.
Woo Min, don't just stand there. Use your strength.
(Command)
What are you doing?
(Right then)
- A car pulled up. - Who's that?
(A car arrives.)
Who is it?
(Someone has come!)
It'll be real bad if two get out.
(They need 1 more woman.)
Who is it?
It's Ji Hyo.
We did it.
(It's Ji Hyo.)
- We did it. - Man-woman couples.
Ji Hyo. You did it for us.
(As Ji Hyo joins them, the conditions are finally met!)
- Thank you, Ji Hyo! - Honestly, I was...
- Good for you. - Did you ruin things?
- I ruined their chances. - Good.
(Ji Hyo managed to escape the sundaeguk restaurant!)
- Well done. - Jong Kook...
Good job.
(Just then)
- Who's that? - Someone's here?
Someone's here?
(A car pulls up.)
- For real? - Someone's here?
(One more person ruins their chances.)
- Oh, no! - Who is it?
(Who is it?)
Who is it?
- No! - Oh, dear...
No!
(Kim Jong Kook)
Hello.
Oh, dear...
(BBQ restaurant: Man-woman couples)
No!
(Now there are 3 men and 2 women.)
Take a seat.
(It's completely silent.)
- Sit down, everyone. - Why are you here?
Sit down.
- You can sit, Ji Hyo. - Why...
(Earlier)
We need another person!
No way. Haha's here.
(Ji Hyo ran away without any plans.)
- Let's go. - She's leaving?
I should follow her. Let's go to the BBQ place.
(He immediately followed her.)
We had a perfect group of three.
(He finds her behavior unacceptable.)
I can't accept it.
I'm going after Ji Hyo.
Until death.
(Ji Hyo was caught by a notorious tracker.)
- Okay, now... - I don't need to eat.
- How about this? - I'm just...
- Let's have the loser leave. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
I don't want to do that. What are you talking about?
Here is the thing.
- When someone betrays me... - Hold on a second!
- One more person came! - Someone is here!
(Another van arrives!)
- I bet it's a man. - Who is it?
It's a man.
Is it Hye Jun?
(If it isn't Hye Jun, they'll be ruined.)
- Hye Jun, come here. - Please.
- Please. - Please.
- Who is it? - Hye Jun!
- Yes! - Yes!
(It's Hye Jun.)
Hye Jun!
- Yes! - Yes!
(Jong Kook's victims welcome her with open arms.)
Hurry over here!
(Now, they have 3 men and 3 women!)
- We're set! - We're set!
- I'm leaving. - No!
- We need to get him. - You can't leave.
- Come on. - We need to get him.
(Unexpected situation)
- Hold on. - I'm leaving.
(Freezing)
You came all the way here.
Ye Eun, come here!
(In the middle of all this)
Instead of getting 5 gold bars as a group of 6 people...
- It's too late to leave. - You can't leave.
- I'll bring her... - It's too late to leave.
misfortune.
- It's too late to leave. - No, it isn't. Go back inside.
(The tracker wants to punish Ji Hyo until the end.)
- Come on. - Go back inside.
- Go back inside. - No.
- Let's eat as a group of six. - No.
(Trying to persuade him)
- Time's up. - That wouldn't make any sense.
(1 minute is left!)
- One minute remains. - It was his plan all along.
- The decision is yours. - Hurry up and restrain him.
I put everything down.
(Getting out of control)
I don't see why the six of us need to succeed in this mission.
(They lost their will to fight.)
One minute remains until the end of the race.
(Meanwhile, they're also notified that they have 1 minute left.)
Hold on.
Hold on. This won't do.
- Jae Seok, get out. - I mean...
Yes, Jae Seok?
(Seok Sam is still on the road.)
Seok Jin, hurry over here. Not much time remains.
I keep getting stuck at a red light.
I'm nearly there.
How much longer until we get there?
- One minute. - One more minute.
We have one minute left, Seok Jin.
(If Seok Jin arrives on time, the Chinese restaurant will live!)
- Now... - What now?
(Haha has an offer.)
Let's have a vote. I think...
Ji Hyo...
- should follow Jong Kook... - Okay.
into wilderness.
- I'm for that idea. - Okay.
(Eureka)
I'll leave with her.
(He accepts the offer instantly.)
Grab her.
- Lift her up. - I'm for that idea. All right.
(Will they reach a dramatic agreement like this?)
- Let's go inside. - The four of you can enjoy eating.
(Meanwhile, at the Chinese restaurant)
We'll eat if Seok Jin arrives on time.
He is here.
Okay!
(It's Seok Jin.)
- Hurry up. - I'm here.
- We're set. - We're set.
(Seok Sam barely made it when 30 seconds were left!)
I kept getting stuck at a red light.
(Chinese restaurant: Odd number)
(As there are 3 people, the conditions are met!)
- We're set. - We're an odd number of people.
- We aren't done yet. - We still have...
- You still have some time. - We still have some time.
(If things stay the same for the next 20 seconds, they'll succeed!)
- Ji Hyo or Hye Jun should go there. - That's right.
- Oh, no! - What?
- No! - Why... For goodness' sake.
- Jae Seok. - Hey, leave!
- Jae Seok, I'm here. - Get out, Hoon!
- Get out! - Why...
- For goodness' sake. - No!
(Kang Hoon arrives.)
Hey, leave!
- Get out! - Get out, Hoon!
Get out!
- Why did you come here? - Why did you come here?
(Chinese restaurant: Odd number)
(It became an even number when 5 seconds were left.)
- Four, three, - Get out!
- Why did you come here? - two,
- one. - Jae Seok told me to come here.
Time's up.
For goodness' sake.
(They failed the mission.)
The Chinese restaurant mission failed.
- Jae Seok told me to come here. - Why... I mean...
Why did you tell everyone to come here?
- Jae Seok. - I didn't know who'd actually come.
(He called everyone because one of them might betray him.)
Hurry up and come to the Chinese restaurant.
Jae Seok, I'll go to the Chinese restaurant.
I'll go there.
(The Chinese restaurant team gets ruined.)
- Why did you... - Hey.
- Other teams might fail to eat. - Seriously.
(Meanwhile, there are 2 men and 2 women at the BBQ place.)
All other restaurant missions failed.
- That sea - That sea
(Singing the cheer song for the L Baseball Team)
Left!
(I don't know that song.)
- Right! - Hoon betrayed me...
- and failed. - Jump!
(Only we'll eat!)
Haha.
- This success is all thanks to me. - The...
- Very best! - Why do you say that?
(The 4 of them acquire a meal and gold bars.)
I made him stay when he tried to run away.
Let's just go inside!
(It's all thanks to him.)
What's wrong with you?
- For goodness' sake! - Okay!
- You called over everyone. - Hold on a second.
(People at the Chinese restaurant are feeling sad again.)
Jae Seok.
- You didn't say Hoon would come. - You know...
You know,
everyone I called over came.
Seriously.
(Subordinates 1, 2, and 3 assembled.)
- I thought you sounded sincere. - You told me to come.
Why did all these people follow my order?
I didn't follow your order.
(Subordinate 1)
- I just came here to eat. - I didn't know...
- that everyone would come. - Jae Seok.
(They lost because they were too loyal.)
You should've locked the door.
Why didn't you do that when you invited so many people?
(They sit down, feeling devastated.)
You know... Seriously.
Hoon can't even eat kimchi.
- For goodness' sake. You're right. - Come here.
The owner of the restaurant is disappointed, okay?
He is a staff member.
- I see. - Come on, Seok Jin.
(Scratching his head)
I'm sorry.
I've had kimchi for weeks. I can't believe it.
(Humble)
(A little too simple for a Chinese restaurant)
- For goodness' sake. - Eating well is important.
You guys don't usually come when I call.
Why did all of you come this time?
You hurriedly asked me to come.
I called three people and all of them came.
You didn't call me once.
- You called me 4 or 5 times. - You know,
- you have good people by your side. - So...
- You're right. - He has a point.
I'm grateful.
(It's all about how you interpret it.)
- I know. - When you think about it...
You should be responsible for our meal.
(While they eat kimchi at a Chinese restaurant,)
It's frozen pork belly.
(pork belly is served here.)
It looks so tasty.
Let's put it on the grill.
(Ms. Free Meals already looks excited.)
Gosh, this meat...
- It looks delicious. - Please give us...
- I know. - tasty rice and kimchi.
- Enjoy the food. - Thank you for the food.
(They grill it quickly...)
Enjoy the food.
(and eat it while it's still chewy.)
(Oh, my!)
(Haha makes a lettuce wrap.)
It's Cheongyang chili.
(Oh, my!)
It tastes incredible.
(The meat is juicy and tender!)
It's so good.
- Gosh, it's tasty. - It's good.
(Inhaling)
(While the 4 winners enjoy frozen pork belly,)
- It's tasty. - It's so good.
(their table doesn't have much food.)
Ji Hyo, show me a smile.
Why the long face...
while filming a show?
(Frowning)
It's a good day.
My goodness.
Seriously.
It tastes so good.
(That man is scary.)
Please pick the favorite employee.
(It's time to pick their favorite employee.)
- Please vote for me. - I vote for Jong Kook.
- Seriously, please vote for me. - I vote for Jong Kook too.
(Haha announces first.)
I'd like to issue...
an apology.
(Out of nowhere)
I misunderstood him.
I thought he was...
a rude jerk.
I thought he was someone who used brute strength for any problems.
(He's thankful that Jong Kook got rid of Ji Hyo instead of him.)
I really appreciated his kindness.
As the favorite employee,
I recommend...
- Employee Kim Jong Kook. - Thank you.
- Kim Jong Kook! - Kim Jong Kook!
(Thus, Employee Kim gets all the votes!)
(Kim Jong Kook, 4 votes)
Thank you so much.
- How scary. - Let's go!
(Jae Seok arrives at the next spot.)
What's this?
(It's Running Trading Company's different office.)
All of our safes are here.
(Their safes are located at one side of the office.)
- Okay! What's this? - Our gold bars must be inside.
That must be it.
(The gold bars they've collected are inside the safes.)
- What? - That's right.
Our gold bars must be inside.
Seok Jin isn't here yet.
He always does that.
When it comes to teamwork...
For goodness' sake.
(Intern Jee shows up.)
- For goodness' sake. - He got coffee too.
- I can see... - Did you bring coffee here?
why senior comedians scolded him so much back then.
What?
- Nothing. - What?
- Did you talk behind my back? - No.
- He was slow back then as well. - I see.
(He's a witness.)
- What was that? - We didn't say anything.
This place is spacious, so we can have a fight.
I'd love that.
- I'd love that. - You think you'll win, right?
- Safes have been broken into! - Oh, my!
(Announcement)
- Safes have been broken into! - What's going on this time?
- Safes have been broken into! - Oh, my!
(Did someone break into the safes?)
- Safes have been broken into! - What's going on this time?
Someone stole the gold bars!
- Did someone steal them? - I bet someone stole them.
Some of the safes...
have been broken into by embezzlers.
What?
(There are spies among us!)
Who are they?
- I'll steal so-and-so's gold bars. - It isn't me.
(Embezzler: "I'll steal so-and-so's gold bars.")
- Who are they? - Your safes have been broken into.
(The embezzlers stole the gold bars throughout the day.)
You can't open or lift up your safe throughout the day.
I had many gold bars.
- You... - Trust me.
It isn't me.
(They immediately begin to suspect each other.)
You...
Why are you looking at me?
I've been suspicious.
(The culprits are among us.)
- It's Haha. - Now,
- there are... - Seriously.
two embezzlers among you.
- Two? - Two? Hoon.
- Embezzlers. - Who are they?
Who are they?
(30 minutes before the opening)
Today, the two of you are...
embezzlers who are...
after other employees' safes.
Every time you succeed in completing a hidden mission,
you can break into the safe of your choice...
and put the gold bars in your safe.
If you fail to complete a hidden mission,
the employees will learn about the embezzlers.
So be careful.
- So there are hidden missions. - Yes.
(Today, while others weren't watching,)
- Since you came to work... - Thank you.
- This one... - Hye Jun.
You did it once!
(the two embezzlers carried out hidden missions.)
You shouldn't have taken things for granted.
Since they failed to complete a hidden mission,
you learned about the existence of the embezzlers.
- Who are the embezzlers? - Who are they?
- I bet you didn't steal them. - It isn't me.
(Who are the embezzlers hiding among them?)
- You don't seem like a thief. - If it's Jong Kook,
- it'll show. - You don't have those vibes.
- Hye Jun. - Yes?
- Why aren't you curious? - What?
- Why aren't you curious? - I didn't understand...
- the rules. - Me neither.
(Both of them claim that they didn't understand.)
- You didn't understand. - I think she is acting.
What a convenient excuse!
(Suspecting)
I can't believe her.
- I didn't understand the rules. - How about...
How about Woo Min?
Where were you earlier?
He wasn't around.
(Just a moment ago)
- You're right. He wasn't around. - Woo Min wasn't around.
(Woo Min left for a moment while they were on standby.)
- I went to my van. - He wasn't around.
- Woo Min wasn't around. - Why did you go to the van?
- Why weren't you around? - He disappeared...
- for a while. - I...
I sweated so much...
that I changed into a new T-shirt.
- How suspicious! - Was that a hidden mission?
- He is suspicious. - Was that a hidden mission?
(No.)
- He is suspicious. - That was so sudden.
(Suspicious)
What's up with you?
- It really isn't me. - Everyone sweats.
(Is Woo Min, who is denying the accusation with a smile, a spy?)
On which station...
will your new drama air?
- tvN. - tvN.
You can...
You can watch it in tvN at 8:45pm on August 3.
(He suddenly starts promoting his show.)
Why did you ask?
(Why so suddenly?)
- I realized that we hadn't asked. - That's right.
- Mondays and Tuesdays. - We didn't get to say it before.
(He could promote the drama thanks to Jae Seok.)
That was a mission, right?
(What was that?)
I bet it was a mission.
- He completed a mission. - How suspicious!
- It's really suspicious. - He completed a mission.
- You... - You usually don't ask such things.
(Did the nation's beloved host make a mistake? Or was it a mission?)
You made us pay attention to them.
- You usually don't do this. - You made us pay attention to them.
(He spots something.)
- Why did you shorten the strap? - You hit me.
All right.
(Putting on sharp eyes)
- A mission, my foot. - You completed a mission.
- What kind of... - Why did you shorten the strap?
- Why did you shorten it so much? - It's suspicious.
- Jae Seok, it's so short. - What's up with your bag?
(It's short.)
- You never wear it that way. - It isn't short. It's fine.
(Suspicious)
He hit me like this.
(There's more.)
- Really? - Yes.
- It must be a mission. - It must be a mission.
- It must be a mission. Look. - What?
(Hitting)
Look. He does it openly now.
- Do you have a mission too? - No.
- Did he hit you like that? - You hit me hard.
(He got hit three times in a row in no time.)
- Look at this. - What?
Hold on. Why did you put your arm around me just now?
What?
Maybe he completed a mission.
- Look at this. He never does it. - I want us to be good friends.
I do it once in a while.
- Earlier... - See? It's suspicious.
(Seok Sam sounds awkward. Could he be?)
- He looks so awkward. - What's going on?
- Seok Jin. - You said you'd quit Running Man...
after getting a big break.
(A tip)
- What? - You know, Seok Jin...
- What was that? - You know,
- he began TikTok again. - TikTok.
- Listen. - Grandpa TikTok.
(The TikTok grandpa has opened his account.)
That's right, Hoon.
- He said that earlier. - That's right.
Well, there is a platform...
("Jee Seok Jin's Video Hits 4.8 Million Views...")
- where you can make... - He said he got many views.
("as Soon as He Returns")
- a lot of money. So... - Okay.
I jokingly said,
(The TikToker who's going to leave the industry...)
"I'll quit Running Man if I get a big break."
That's right.
(is an embezzler?)
"I'll quit Running Man and leave this industry."
You must be curious about the current state of the safes.
- Yes. - Our gold bars got stolen.
As a penalty for the failed hidden mission,
two safes will be chosen at random...
and opened right away.
(The safes get chosen at random.)
- Is it good to get picked? - Will they get chosen at random?
It's time to make deductions.
Hold on. You got timid.
- No, I didn't. - "Will they get chosen at random?"
Why would I get timid?
- You got timid. - It has no effect on me.
Anyone who has gold bars is an embezzler.
(If he stole gold bars, the safe will be filled.)
Please don't misunderstand. It isn't me.
- Let's catch the real embezzlers. - The first safe...
The first safe...
- is Hoon's. We'll open it. - Hoon.
(First safe reveal, Kang Hoon)
- This is good. - We got you, you punk.
- You suspect me. - We'll pick the second one...
(Picking another person right after)
- and open them at once. - Okay.
- Hoon. - All right.
I hope I get picked.
Same here. I want my name cleared.
The second safe is Seok Jin's.
(Seok Jin gets picked right away.)
- Really? - That's incredible.
- My goodness. - He is a prime suspect.
He became speechless.
- What? I'm fine. - Now,
- your eyes... - Seriously.
(Suspicious)
- He looks suspicious. - It isn't me.
Everyone, it isn't me.
An employee from the Audit Team will open...
(The audit team's member will reveal the safe.)
- Hoon's safe first. - I got my gold bars stolen.
(Director Myung Jae is today's auditor.)
Myung Jae will do it.
- I'll open Hoon's safe first. - Good.
His perm came out well.
(Laughing)
- Hoon. - I'll open...
(Isn't Kang Hoon's safe stolen?)
- Hoon's safe. - What did I say earlier?
Okay.
I'll open Hoon's safe.
It's empty. His gold bars got stolen.
His gold bars got stolen.
(Kang Hoon)
- It's empty. - It's empty.
(An embezzler stole Hoon's safe.)
- Is it empty? - His gold bars got stolen.
- His gold bars got stolen. - His gold bars got stolen.
- His gold bars got stolen. - It's empty.
I'll steal Hoon's gold bars.
(Embezzler)
(All of his gold bars got moved to an embezzler's safe.)
- His gold bars got stolen. - His gold bars got stolen.
- It's empty. - Maybe it's staged.
(Who is the embezzler that took Kang Hoon's gold bars?)
- It's empty. - His gold bars got stolen.
- Maybe it's staged. - It's empty.
Hold on a second.
If Seok Jin has many gold bars,
- it's him. - It's game over.
- I... - It depends on...
(What about Seok Sam's safe, the usual suspect?)
- the quantity. - I'm not an embezzler.
- Let's see the quantity. - I'll open Seok Jin's safe.
(Jee Seok Jin)
Seok Sam.
If he stole from others, he'd have many gold bars.
Let's check out Seok Sam's safe.
(Laughing)
Hye Jun, you look so giddy.
- You're so anxious. - You...
In 1, 2, 3.
- One, two, three, four... - They're the ones he received.
(There are many gold bars!)
- My goodness. - Four, six, seven.
- They're the ones he received. - Hold on.
- Hold on. Mister. - How many are there?
- This is... - I'm not an embezzler.
- Guys, it really isn't me. - Why are there so many?
- You only gave him two, right? - I'm getting framed.
(Suspicion growing upon seeing so many gold bars)
I'm getting framed.
- How many did you receive? - I'm getting framed.
- I'm getting framed. - How many did you receive?
- Why are there so many? - They're...
- They're mine. - Why are there so many?
- Why are there so many? - You didn't even get a proper meal.
- I know. You failed the mission. - How many are there?
- Why are there so many? - How many are there?
Eleven.
Eleven?
- He is ridiculous. It's game over. - That's more than what I've earned.
Eleven? Listen.
- It's impossible to have 11. - I...
- Don't lie. - Listen.
(Suspect Jee begins explaining himself.)
I had three at first.
Listen to me carefully.
- The real culprit... - There is no need to explain.
- Just get ready for jail. - No, I...
- Hold on. - Let's hear him out.
- "Just get ready for jail." - This is important.
(Feeling rushed)
All right, everyone.
- Just go to jail. - Listen to me carefully.
I'll explain why I have 11.
- Just serve your time in jail. - That's right. You should do that.
(Beginning public protesting)
- Then you'll learn your lesson. - Serve your time.
- Listen to me. - Serve your time.
In the beginning,
I received two.
(He gave 2 gold bars to Jae Seok at first.)
Then I stole Jae Seok's gold bar, so I had three.
(Then he stole 1 without Jae Seok knowing.)
- No. - They're really mine. I'm serious.
- He stole a gold bar. - He stole a gold bar.
- When did you steal it? - As for that...
- He needs to go to jail... - That's right.
- for theft anyway. - He needs to go to jail.
You gave a gold bar to everyone except for me.
I took one then.
It makes no sense whatsoever.
- Seriously. - Anyway, our team won.
(He stole one...)
(and won one through a mission.)
- Yes! - You didn't listen.
(He claims he got 11 bars somehow.)
That's how I have 11 gold bars.
I'm getting framed. Please don't misunderstand.
- I'm disappointed. - Who are the real embezzlers?
(But it looks like no one believes him.)
You'll be our suspect.
- You'll be our suspect. - You'll have the last chance...
to catch the embezzlers.
- What is it? - We hid hints...
on the embezzlers in this place.
In five minutes,
find all the hints and apprehend the embezzlers.
(Gather the hints in those and find the 2 embezzlers!)
- Who are the embezzlers? - I really want to catch them.
After five minutes, you'll turn in the names of two people...
you think are the embezzlers.
- Okay. - Okay. Let's go.
- I really want to catch them. - All right.
- The second floor too? - Let's go.
It isn't me.
Check the tables.
(They begin the search.)
(Will they be able to catch the two embezzlers...)
What is this umbrella doing here?
- Can we go outside? - Let's go outside.
(who stole gold bars?)
Who wants to go upstairs?
Are there two embezzlers?
Haha, let's go upstairs.
Are hints upstairs as well?
Yes, they are.
- Let's go. - All right.
Where are the R stickers?
Woo Min.
(Right then)
Is anything written inside?
"The oldest member..."
- "isn't an embezzler." - What was that?
"Isn't an embezzler."
(The oldest member isn't an embezzler.)
The oldest member isn't a suspect.
(The suspicious Seok Sam isn't an embezzler!)
- I'm not an embezzler. - Aren't you an embezzler?
For goodness' sake.
- We don't have much time. - I'm not it.
(They begin searching outside after excluding the usual suspect.)
Is anyone good with computers?
What?
(Right then, Jong Kook found something on the laptop.)
- Hey, Seok Jin. - Please don't misunderstand.
What is it? It's a hint.
"One embezzler starred in a thriller."
So it isn't me.
(One embezzler starred in a thriller.)
- Hey, Hoon. - Yes?
Did you star in a thriller?
A thriller?
- A thriller. - Hye Jun.
- A thriller? - Hye Jun.
- Yes? - That genre...
That genre...
Hye Jun starred in a thriller.
- Yes, she did. - Yes.
- She did many such works. - "A Shop for Killers."
- That's a thriller, right? - Yes.
(Kim Hye Jun, "A Shop for Killers")
That's a thriller.
Hoon was in a thriller too.
- Which one? - Which one do you mean?
- What? "Hunter with a Scalpel." - Is that a thriller?
(Kang Hoon, "Hunter with a Scalpel")
- Hey, Ji Hyo! - I think so.
- What? - Ji Hyo was in a thriller.
(The one person who starred in a thriller is...)
It was titled "Intruder" or something.
"Intruder" wasn't the only one.
(It's an embezzler for sure.)
"Night Has Come."
He fits the description.
Ji Hyo was in a thriller.
(That means one of the four is a suspect, at least.)
Hye Jun was in a thriller too.
"One embezzler starred in a thriller."
That's one hint.
In that case...
Jae Seok filmed a thriller.
- Which one? - On "Infinite Challenge."
(On "Infinite Challenge?")
- "Infinite Challenge." - He filmed a thriller on that show.
- A drama. Was that a thriller? - Right?
- "Infinite Company." - "Infinite Company."
- Was that a thriller? - It was Writer Kim Eun Hee...
(Director Jang Hang Jun and Writer Kim Eun Hee's...)
and Director Jang Hang Jun's work.
(short drama, "2026 Infinite Company")
Employee Ha.
(Haha starred in it too.)
It was a thriller. He starred in it.
(It's actually categorized as a thriller.)
- That makes Jae Seok a suspect. - Right. It was a thriller.
- I think it's Jae Seok. - I think it's Jae Seok.
(The 6 people are named as suspects.)
I think it's him. The thriller hint narrowed things down.
Seok Sam.
- Jae Seok. - Yes?
I think you're a spy.
- Who are you calling a spy? - You know,
- it all makes sense. - Jae Seok, I think you're a spy.
- You were in a thriller, right? - No, I wasn't.
(Starting aggressive questioning based on "Infinite Company")
- "Infinite Company." - "Infinite Company."
- Well, I was in it. - You were the lead in a thriller...
- by Director Jang Hang Jun. - Yes, I was.
That's right. It was a masterpiece.
That isn't...
- That isn't important. - Seriously.
So we have three suspects.
- I rewatched it recently. - Okay.
(Giving an irrelevant answer)
It's entertaining.
Back then, people said that it was boring.
(Dumbfounded)
- It's entertaining. - I think it's entertaining.
I watch it sometime too.
(He fell for it.)
- In any case, you... - Okay.
(He starts inferring after getting himself together.)
and Hye Jun...
- I'm not an embezzler. - Jae Seok and Hye Jun.
(That's right.)
Woo Min was...
- only in thrillers. - A thriller.
- A thriller. - "Weak Hero."
- Were you on "Weak Hero?" - Yes.
- In Season 1? Whom did you play? - The MMA fighter in Season 1.
(This was Woo Min.)
That was you.
Seok Jin, why didn't you star in "Weak Hero?"
It must be because you aren't a hero.
If it's only about weakness, I'll be the lead.
(He's the weakest, but no one is giving him a role.)
- Seok Sam, did you find anything? - Yes.
"One embezzler starred in a thriller."
(Revealing the hint that everyone knows)
I heard that one.
For your information, I never starred in a thriller.
(Of course.)
Why does everything have an R sticker?
- What? - Oh, my.
- What? - What is it?
- Here it is. - Is something written there?
"One embezzler won the Newcomer Award."
Did you win the Newcomer Award?
- Hoon won the Newcomer Award. - Hye Jun too?
(Ji Ye Eun, Best Rookie Award)
(Kang Hoon, Best Rookie Award)
Woo Min too?
Jae Seok won the Newcomer Award too...
(Kim Hye Jun, Best Rookie Award)
(Cha Woo Min, Best Rookie Award)
- as his alter ego, Yu San Seul. - You're right.
(Yu San Seul, Best Rookie Award)
(One embezzler has won the Best Rookie Award.)
I think it's Hye Jun!
You won it too.
- It's Hye Jun. - It's Hye Jun.
(She was in a thriller, and she won the Best Rookie Award.)
- You won it too. - I never starred in a thriller.
It's Hye Jun.
- Hoon starred in a thriller too. - It's Hye Jun.
(Right then, Kang Hoon appears.)
Hoon fits the descriptions too.
- Did Hoon star in a thriller? - But Hoon...
- never won the Newcomer Award. - I don't know...
if it counts as a thriller.
But Hoon...
- Did he win the Newcomer Award? - Yes.
Why are you so flustered?
- Did I win the Newcomer Award? - Did you win the Newcomer Award?
- MBC. - MBC. Yes, I did.
(Kang Hoon won the Best Rookie Award at MBC!)
- Did you win the Newcomer Award? - Yes.
He won it too.
Why? Who are the suspects?
(Calm)
They're Hoon and Hye Jun.
(Gullible)
It's Hoon.
- I say that since I'm not it. - You aren't it?
I don't understand the rules. I can't be an embezzler.
I think you're acting.
I'm serious.
I don't think there are any more hints here.
(He starts searching the back by himself.)
Maybe there are no hints here. I don't see any hints.
(One embezzler has a sibling.)
Then...
Hold on.
That's me.
(One embezzler has a sibling.)
(He has an older sister.)
Hold on.
I'll hide it for now.
(Why does he hide a hint?)
(He moves after hiding a hint that makes him a suspect.)
I need to go outside to go upstairs, right?
(He goes to the 2nd floor without sharing the hint.)
(Full of people)
Everyone is there.
(He looks for hints alone in a different room.)
Are there no more hints?
What? Why is there an R sticker?
(The R mark)
What? "One embezzler..."
(He finds another hint.)
How will I get rid of it?
(Why is he getting rid of a hint again?)
(Why does he keep discarding the hints?)
I'll steal Ye Eun's gold bars.
Today, the two of you are embezzlers who are...
(One of the embezzlers is...)
after other employees' safes.
(Kang Hoon.)
I don't have that image.
Every time you succeed in...
(Upon completing a hidden mission,)
completing a hidden mission, you can break into the safe...
of your choice and put the gold bars in your safe.
(they can steal gold bars from an employee of their choice.)
I should work hard.
(One of the hidden missions)
Secondly, make one team...
- fail the lunch mission. - Each restaurant...
(Hidden Mission 1: Make 1 team fail the lunch mission)
has its own conditions for dining. If you successfully gather...
(When the lunch mission was announced...)
according to the conditions, you'll be able to eat...
- at that restaurant. - So there are conditions.
If you fail, you'll only get rice and kimchi.
That can't happen.
- Then Kang Hoon won't get to eat. - Kang Hoon...
- He'll only have rice. - He can't eat kimchi.
What are the conditions?
I can't have kimchi with rice.
(Embezzler 2)
I want to make that embezzler fail and eat lunch.
No. I should do the mission and skip lunch.
This time, I should do it properly...
Odd number for the Chinese restaurant.
(Embezzler 2: Odd number of people required for the Chinese restaurant)
Age and odd number.
Would I be seen here?
(He heads to the Chinese restaurant after reading the embezzler's text.)
We'll be able to eat if only Seok Sam comes here.
(In hiding)
- Hurry up! - I'm here.
(Just as the Chinese restaurant team was about to succeed…)
- I'm here. - We've succeeded.
- We've succeeded. - We've succeeded.
The traffic lights...
- No! - No!
(He quickly enters.)
- No! - Why?
- Seriously! - The Chinese restaurant members...
(That's how he succeeded in the hidden mission!)
- have failed. - Why did you call everyone here?
Jae Seok!
(Will Embezzler Kang Hoon be able to avoid getting caught?)
That's...
(Woo Min found another hint.)
It wouldn't be here, right?
(4. One embezzler isn't married.)
What is this? It's here.
(What is this?)
(One embezzler is a man.)
One embezzler is a man!
(5. One embezzler is a man.)
- What? - What?
One of the embezzlers is a man!
- One of them is a man. - How did you find that?
I found it on the Post-it note!
(Excited)
(Every clue points to Kang Hoon.)
- Okay. - Let's find out who this is.
- Okay. - Okay. One embezzler is a man.
- What? - Where were you?
- What? - I've been searching this place.
- Okay. One embezzler is a man. - Where were you?
(He runs into them right after getting rid of the clue.)
- What? - I've been searching this place.
- He's suspicious. - Hold on.
- You found nothing? - There's nothing there.
(Flustered)
It's even weirder that there isn't one.
You could act like you didn't see it.
Isn't it weird that there wasn't any clue here?
(Excited)
I found one clue. But...
(Changing his words)
I found 1 on the 1st floor.
- It's weird that it wasn't here. - No.
This is a new room. It's weird that there's no hint.
It's definitely him.
(Anxious)
- We got you! - We got you!
- Jong Kook. - We got you.
(Rushed)
I have an important hint.
- Let us see. - Share it with us.
It's him. You know it, right? We caught him.
Goodness.
(Embezzler Hoon becomes a likely suspect in no time.)
It can't go on like this. I'm the only guest...
(Feeling discouraged)
Did you find the hints?
No.
- I found one. - What is it?
What is it?
(Trying to win over the old love interest by dropping a hint)
Hoon! Come on.
Does anyone have a sister?
(Pretending not to know)
- Jae Seok. - Jae Seok?
- You have 10 seconds left. - We have 10 seconds left!
(They have only 10 seconds now.)
Tell me what this is as well.
- I'll tell you later. - Okay.
We'll find you. What is this?
(It's their last chance to find the hint.)
We already know this.
They wouldn't have hidden it in such a complicated way.
The race has ended. Please gather here.
(Their search ends.)
"Have different occupations?"
(The embezzlers have different professions.)
How are we supposed to find them in five minutes?
(The last discussion before the vote)
I really couldn't find them.
I found three.
(The hints)
- What? - Woo Min...
- Share them with us. - Tell us.
The embezzlers have different occupations.
The oldest member isn't an embezzler.
One embezzler isn't married.
If they have different occupations...
His hint says the embezzlers have different occupations.
(The embezzlers have different professions.)
- Different occupations. - Right.
They have different occupations.
(Then the person with Hoon's profession is...)
So there's one actor and one comedian.
- An actor and... - There's definitely one actor.
(The 4 actors are crossed off the list.)
- A comedian... - A singer.
(Embezzler 1, Kang Hoon)
Did anyone release an album?
(Then it must be one of these four.)
One from "Express Delivery: Mongolia Edition."
- Goodness. - We don't know that song.
It could be a comedian and a singer.
(One of them is Kang Hoon's accomplice.)
- Exactly. - Right.
(The embezzlers have different professions.)
- There's Haha. - I think...
- one is a Running Man member. - Yes.
- One side? - One person.
- And one guest? - And...
- That's right. - one of the guests.
- That's for sure. - That's for sure.
- Right. - Then you'll just think it's me.
(Anxious)
- They have different occupations. - Right.
(Thanks to Woo Min, the net is closing in.)
- They're all actors. - They're actors.
He came out from searching a new room by himself...
and said he found no hints.
(Sharing how Hoon is suspicious)
- Who said that? - Kang Hoon.
It was one of the rooms. He came out and pretended...
- like there was nothing. - He said there was nothing, but...
- Ye Eun... - But I shared it with Ye Eun.
(Innocent)
- He showed it to me. - Share that with us.
"One embezzler..." This one also includes me.
(Sharing the hint to avoid suspicion)
- "Has a sister." - "Has a sister."
Did you ever win the Newcomer Award?
Hold on. When we opened the safe earlier...
When we opened the safe earlier,
he should have been upset since there was no gold bar.
But he didn't seem surprised.
- There's nothing. - There's nothing.
(He saw the safe that had been emptied.)
- His safe was robbed. - It got robbed.
- It got robbed. - It got robbed.
- It got robbed. - Why is there nothing?
(Detective Kim caught the culprit's calm expression.)
- Did they take it all? - This...
He should have been upset since there was no gold bar.
But he didn't seem surprised.
- Isn't this all an act? - I've always been...
- I think he was always like that. - Really?
(Defending)
I've always been like that here. That's why I was always a suspect.
- He's not that energetic. - That's why I was always a suspect.
(Everyone agrees.)
A thriller?
(Scratching)
He wasn't surprised. He didn't say, "Where are the gold bars?"
(Suspicious again)
He usually doesn't seem to get surprised a lot.
I've been on variety shows a lot.
Is that so?
(Embarrassed)
Jae Seok and Hye Jun.
(Thanks, Ye Eun.)
- I think it's them. - Should we gather the hints again?
He sometimes seemed like the culprit.
(While Hoon avoided his suspicion)
Should we get the hints again?
- What should we do? - Who is it among the entertainers?
What was the hint?
Who here has a sister?
(One of the embezzlers has a female sibling.)
(Me!)
- Go that side. - Go there.
(Me too)
- Then... - Jae Seok as well? Right.
He has an older sister. Then those who aren't suspects...
are Jong Kook, Se Chan, and Ye Eun.
- We didn't star in a thriller. - It's one of them.
- You didn't? - It's one of them.
But "Infinite Company" was...
- Also... - You two were in a thriller.
I guess "Infinite Company" was a thriller.
- We should count it as a thriller. - No...
(It's him!)
I didn't even consider that. It's just Hye Jun.
- Why? - What did you hide in your stomach?
(Flaring his nostrils)
I didn't even consider that.
- It's just Hye Jun. - Why?
What did you hide in your stomach?
(Exchanging glances)
- What is it? - I mean...
I feel like it's Haha, but Jae Seok's acting...
- is so awkward. - He's trying to act.
(Ye Eun and Jong Kook think Jae Seok is the embezzler...)
- His reactions are awkward. - Right.
(based on his expression.)
I think we'll figure it out if we keep going a little longer.
Let's keep going.
(Is it the embezzler's terrible acting?)
- No. - But...
(Or is he really innocent?)
No, I...
- Did the culprits do the missions? - This is driving me crazy.
Who did the hidden mission?
(Smart)
- This is driving me crazy. - Find the person...
who did the hidden mission.
- It's Hye Jun. - But what was the mission...
(Avoiding a talk about the hidden mission)
- earlier? - We wouldn't know.
Earlier, during the break,
(Seok Sam's question reminds him of what happened earlier.)
they sent us upstairs as soon as we got out.
- Right. - Right.
- You remember that, right? - That's right.
(Everyone rested on the second floor.)
Please go upstairs.
- Was it the hidden mission? - During that time,
he brushed...
He was busy moving around, saying he was going to brush his teeth.
That's right. Jae Seok did that.
- Grasshopper? - Yes.
- He kept... - Jae Seok did that.
He asked why filming hadn't started yet.
Brushing your teeth seems like an odd hidden mission.
- No, I mean... - Your scheme is too obvious.
- The filming... - He was there the whole time.
Jae Seok started...
- brushing his teeth first. - He asked why filming...
- hadn't started yet. - Tooth-brushing as the mission?
No. I'm not saying brushing the teeth was the mission.
That's when he got up...
- and started moving around. - He got up.
His hand is wet.
(Jae Seok carried out the hidden mission,)
That's when he started moving around.
(saying he was brushing his teeth.)
That's an obvious scheme.
It's him. He's the culprit.
- This is crazy. - Seriously.
(Is there an embezzler among Jae Seok and Haha?)
- It feels nice to be misunderstood. - Now,
you'll split up and vote for who you think...
(They scatter and start voting for an embezzler.)
- the embezzler is. - Okay.
The embezzler's votes will not be counted.
(The embezzlers' votes won't be included.)
- I think it's Jae Seok. - Who is it?
If you catch both of them, the top two members...
with the most gold bars will receive the prizes.
- What? - If you fail to catch both of them,
you will receive the penalty.
Running Man is getting interesting.
The employees who write the names of the embezzlers...
(The employee who catches the embezzlers...)
(will be excluded from the penalty.)
will be exempted from getting the penalty.
(Exempted)
- Really? - That's...
- Goodness. - The final vote will now begin.
(That means they can survive if they get the correct one.)
Okay. I've made up my mind.
(Time to vote)
- Seriously. - I'll trust you and write his name.
They're whispering over there.
- Did the culprits do the missions? - What time did you get here?
(Random)
- Why do you ask? - What time did you get here?
- Did you get here at 8am? - This is driving me crazy.
What time did you get here? At 8am?
(Hoon drops clues as the last measure.)
Yes. It was 8am.
(Staring)
- Why did you suddenly ask that? - Is it Haha?
- It's Haha. - They ask you to come quickly...
(Acting innocent)
- if you're the spy. - Look. Jae Seok is framing me.
(They split up and begin voting individually.)
Jong Kook.
Asking when...
we got here out of the blue?
That's why...
(Woo Min chose Kang Hoon.)
They don't suspect me in the first place.
(He got himself suspected by talking too much.)
Kang Hoon seems very suspicious.
(Hye Jun chose Kang Hoon.)
You wrote Kang Hoon, right?
(Kang Hoon received all the votes from his fellow actors.)
Isn't it Kang Hoon?
- I think it's Kang Hoon. - Don't you think it's Kang Hoon?
- Kang Hoon! - Yes?
Aren't you the embezzler?
- Are you asking if I'm the culprit? - Yes. Aren't you the one?
It's not me.
(Hoon's clues)
You're not married.
(Been in a thriller, won the Rookie Award,)
- It's not me. - You even won the Newcomer Award.
- You won the Newcomer Award. - I did.
(has a female sibling, is single, and is a male.)
(Hoon is about to be arrested.)
- All the hints... - All the hints...
- I can't defend myself. - I think...
(In order for the embezzlers to survive,)
I think they were trying to make it confusing.
(another accomplice should not be revealed.)
No.
(Embezzler 1, potential accomplices)
It's Haha and Kang Hoon. I'll change to that.
What were the hints again?
- Not married. - The hints...
One embezzler is a man.
(One of the embezzlers is a male.)
- Starred in a thriller. - One is a man and one is a woman.
- Really? - Yes.
- Hold on. - They're both...
- One embezzler is a man. - One embezzler...
(They take out the clue again.)
- is a man. - Hold on!
If the hint says, "One embezzler is a man..."
- They could both be men. - It's likely that they're both men.
- Hold on. - It's likely that they're both men.
(Detective Kook got it precisely.)
They could both be men?
"One embezzler is a man."
(One of the embezzlers is a male.)
It didn't say, "Only one of the embezzlers..."
- "is a man." - That's right!
- "One embezzler." - They could both be men.
(Certain)
- They could both be men. - Two men.
Didn't it say the embezzlers were a man and a woman?
- No. - It said one was a man, right?
It said one embezzler was a man.
(Embezzler 1, potential accomplices)
We're being deceived by them.
- By whom? - I think it's Kang Hoon...
and Haha.
- Haha? - Kang Hoon and Haha?
They could both be men.
(Who is the accomplice...)
That's possible.
(among Jae Seok, Jong Kook, Haha, and Se Chan?)
(Earlier during the search,)
(Kang Hoon got rid of that decisive hint.)
"A family member of one embezzler is a TV personality."
- This one... - I'm...
(Wife, wife, real brother)
(One of them is an accomplice.)
I should just keep this.
I think I should get rid of this.
(Hoon got rid of the important clue.)
They gave it to us like that to play with our minds.
(But...)
(The detective made sure to narrow down the suspects.)
The hint saying that both of them are men would be somewhere.
(Who is the suspect among the three?)
- They might both be men? - That's possible.
- One of them is a man. - They could both be men.
That's possible.
What is it? What's the title?
(Thinking)
"Hunter with a Scalpel."
(Jae Seok was looking at the hint about the embezzler being single.)
- Were you the hunter? - I was a police officer.
Hold on.
"One embezzler..."
"is not married."
(One of the embezzlers is single.)
- But... - They could both be single.
(It could apply to both embezzlers too.)
- They could both be single. - Of course.
If we go with that assumption...
If, for example, we say...
Kang Hoon is the culprit...
- A different occupation. - A different occupation...
- and single. - Yang Se Chan?
You're suddenly saying it's me? Would it be that obvious?
(Se Chan was not suspected until now.)
- What? - It's not me. It really isn't me.
- Why, you... - It really isn't me.
It's not me.
(Suspicious)
- Se Chan! - How can you assume it's me...
just because one of them is unmarried?
It could be him, for all we know.
Are we guessing it might be Se Chan?
(Confused)
Didn't Jae Seok just try to throw us off?
(Embezzler 1, candidate accomplices)
Maybe it's Jae Seok and Hoon.
It could be those two.
- That's right. - But...
This is a tough one.
I haven't the slightest.
I have no clue.
Why did you tell everyone to come here?
(Candidate 1, Yu Jae Seok)
- Four, three, - Get out!
(Yelling at Kang Hoon at the Chinese restaurant was the cause.)
- two, one. - Why did you come here?
- Jae Seok told me to come here. - Leave!
- Time's up. - He didn't say Hoon was coming too.
You got caught in your own trap.
He keeps saying...
(Candidate 2, Yang Se Chan)
(Is his chest dance a hidden mission?)
he's SAN of ATEEZ today. His armpits!
(Or is pickpocketing a mission?)
Even thugs wear more clothes than that.
Just look at him.
(Candidate 3, Haha)
The two of you, just leave.
(Haha seemed extra jealous today.)
- You can partner up. - Why?
- What's wrong with you today? - What do you mean?
Haha could be the embezzler.
(Staring intently)
It's really not me.
- Isn't it? - No.
I got fooled by you in this exact situation once.
You caught me last time. Anyway, it's not me.
It's really not me.
Why are you suddenly suspecting me?
(Will he be able to catch Kang Hoon's accomplice?)
I'm completely lost. Everyone's so good at lying.
Whoever it is, you're totally shameless.
I've got no clue.
Okay.
I'm going out on a limb here.
(Yang Se Chan)
(Jae Seok pushes it until the end.)
- I'm going out on a limb here. - Let me see.
Se Chan?
It really isn't me. You have to believe me.
- It's either Se Chan or Jae Seok. - It's not me.
I think it's Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok, Kang Hoon)
I'm betting it all on Jae Seok.
(Detective Kim chooses Jae Seok in the end.)
He's a terrible actor.
(Jae Seok, Hye Jun)
Are you sure it isn't you?
(Jae Seok acted strange.)
The two embezzlers have different occupations, right?
Okay.
The embezzler has a sister,
and Hoon has an older sister.
(Haha is getting ready to be nominated one day.)
I think it's Hoon and Haha.
I've made my decision.
(Kang Hoon, Haha)
The suspense is killing me.
(Everyone is done choosing the empezzlers.)
- I can't make up my mind. - I haven't the slightest.
- I really can't tell. - I don't know. It could be anyone.
(What could be the answer?)
Whoever it is, you're really shameless.
(The final reveal)
For the final reveal,
you'll head to the Judgment Stand.
I'm dying to find out who they are.
(The employees win only if they correctly guess both embezzlers.)
They're the worst.
- No way. - What's this?
What's this?
- Water? I see. - A firework.
(Kang Hoon has realized his fate as an embezzler.)
I have no clue.
This was tough to guess.
I went out on a limb at the end...
because Se Chan fooled me...
- like this before. - Really?
Jae Seok always suspects me.
- There's something about him. - I know.
- He's the only one in a vest. - Hold on.
If you think it's me, it'll seem like me. You know that.
Se Chan and Hoon don't make a great crime duo.
(The combination)
- I agree. - Exactly.
Wait, the two guys dumped by Ye Eun?
- What? - Come on.
(The two men Ye Eun rejected?)
(What?)
- I think that's it! - I mean it.
(I'm sorry.)
- Think about it. - How could she have dumped us?
We weren't dumped.
I want to make that clear.
(Putting his hands on his waist)
- Hold on. Ye Eun. - We were never together.
- We rejected her. - I think I'm right.
(Did the embezzler turn dark after betraying by Ddochi?)
The two men she rejected.
- The men she rejected. - And you made a special out of it?
Am I right?
(An avid viewer)
I think he's right!
The men Ye Eun dumped.
(Exhilarated)
In other words, MYD.
All right. I'll now reveal who you voted for as the embezzlers.
- Sure. - This is insane.
- The results are in. - Right.
(Final candidates of embezzlers)
Kang Hoon received seven votes.
(Kang Hoon)
Kang Hoon and...
- And Jae Seok received four votes. - What?
(Jae Seok)
- What? - It really isn't me.
(Jae Seok will be put on trial in the end.)
- Please get up on the stand. - Are you kidding me?
Jae Seok...
(The embezzlers will win if Se Chan or Haha are one of them.)
- What? - Please get up on the stand.
You think it was two male embezzlers.
Also, anyone who correctly guessed...
- the embezzlers will be exempt... - Did anyone guess it right?
(Those who wrote the candidates for an embezzler...)
(will not be punished.)
- from punishment today. - Really?
- I think I got it wrong. - I think I got it wrong too.
(They wrote Haha's name.)
If you two are the embezzlers,
- fireworks will go off. - Got it.
If you're not,
something else will go off.
It really isn't me!
(Is Jae Seok an embezzler?)
- I can't believe you people. - But...
All right. One...
(Revealing the result)
They're the worst.
(Jae Seok was the prime suspect believed to be Hoon's partner.)
- Two. - They could both be men.
It really isn't me!
(Is Jae Seok an embezzler?)
Three.
(He isn't!)
I told you it wasn't me.
- I told you it wasn't me. - I see.
- I told you earlier. - It's not him.
(Then either Haha or Se Chan is an embezzler.)
Hoon's one of the embezzlers.
- Hoon's one of them. - We got Hoon right.
Kang Hoon is one of the embezzlers,
- but Jae Seok isn't. - I told you.
(Who is the accomplice?)
- See? - What did I tell you?
It's Ji Hyo.
It's Haha.
(Haha suddenly suspects Ji Hyo.)
- I can't believe Ji Hyo. - Who is it?
Woo Min, don't tell me it's you.
- Of course it isn't. - If it's you...
(Se Chan suddenly suspects Woo Min.)
If it were you and Hoon,
I'm going to delete all your phone numbers.
The embezzler who successfully fooled you is...
(Who hid the stars who had a thick face until the end?)
Who is it?
- It's Se Chan. - See?
(Yang Ssaebssaeb fooled everyone right up until the last second.)
Nice!
- You two... - Yes?
are embezzlers after what's inside...
the employees' safes.
They'll suspect it's me!
At least I'm nowhere near being a suspect.
- Here are your secret missions. - Sure.
(A hidden mission that has a chance to make up for them)
A,
make at least three people angry at you.
Hye Jun's only 32.
Hye Jun was born in 1995.
- So she's around Ye Eun's age? - She's in her 20s.
She's not around Ye Eun's age. Ye Eun is way older.
(Seizing the opportunity)
Ye Eun's a year older.
- I'm only a year older. - She looks...
- way older than her. - Do you want your gums to collapse?
(Mission success!)
My gums to collapse?
- Leave. - Someone will fill in for you.
(Sneakily grabbing the file)
You can leave.
Why should I quit for wearing shorts?
(Making a bat)
Come back in longer pants. No one else is in shorts.
(Looking for an opportunity)
- I... - Why are you acting so cocky?
(Hitting)
(Mission success, a 2nd time!)
- Is that allowed? - Why are you acting so cocky?
(Shining in his role)
Should I go back to my old self?
(I should complete my missions too.)
- How rude of you to talk... - Come on.
- If someone on my team... - What's his name again?
- It's Yoo Myung. - Let us talk, will you?
- Yoo Myung? - Yes, Yoo Myung.
Hey, Yoo Myung.
- Who? - Yoo Myung?
(Providing support)
Who's Yoo Myung?
- He's already famous, okay? - I can't believe him.
- Are you kidding me? - What is it?
(They easily pissed off 3 members since that's what they do best.)
- This brat... - Did you tell him the wrong name?
I can't believe him.
For now, I'll raid Ji Hyo's safe.
I'm taking what's in Jae Seok's safe.
(Ye Chan, Hoon)
I had eight which brings my total to...
B, make at least one team fail the lunch mission.
We need to sabotage the team that's least expecting it.
(Se Chan called Hoon before Jae Seok called him.)
I'm on my way to the Chinese restaurant.
- Hoon, if I press my buttons, - Yes?
it means it's urgent, so rush in here.
I'll enter without taking your call.
You don't have to. That's your signal to rush in.
(Hoon joins them as soon as Se Chan calls him.)
Got it.
(They're about to win with an odd number.)
- What? - Where were you just now?
I was kicked out of the sundaeguk restaurant.
(Calling Kang Hoon)
At the sundaeguk restaurant, there has to be...
There are three people here.
- What happened there? - Because Ji Hyo happened...
(Hoon, get over here fast.)
Se Chan's calling.
(Kang Hoon, who was in hiding, makes his entry as planned!)
(They successfully sabotaged the lunch mission.)
- No! - Why... For goodness' sake.
- Jae Seok. - Hey, leave!
Jae Seok, I'm here.
(Shameless.)
Get out, Hoon!
- Why did you come here? - He told me to come.
(They earned another chance to embezzle the company.)
I'll take what's in Ye Eun's safe.
I'll explain this to Hoon later...
and steal from his safe.
(Se Chan, Hoon, Ye Eun)
I'll take what he has for now...
(Hoon emptied his safe to earn trust.)
and explain this to him later.
Lastly,
get someone to say you're funny.
It isn't easy to get someone...
to call you funny.
Some of the safes...
(As Ssaebssaeb predicted, they failed the last mission.)
have been broken into by embezzlers.
(Kang Hoon's safe was emptied already.)
- It's empty. - They're gone.
- His gold bars got stolen. - It's empty.
(Decoy)
- His gold bars got stolen. - They got stolen.
- His gold bars got stolen. - It's empty.
(The hair net digger avoided the suspicion wisely.)
- Maybe this was staged. - His is empty.
(During the last search for embezzler clues)
What's this?
(Clue discovered)
(One embezzler has a two-syllable name.)
(A clue that puts the spotlight on Hoon as a suspect)
(He gets rid of it immediately.)
(The Ssaeb-Hoon Duo hid their identities...)
(and took control of the game.)
- No way. - I told you I saw his expression!
(They failed to catch Se Chan, so the embezzlers won!)
- I told you I saw his expression! - Jae Seok got it right.
- You got it right. - Did you get it right?
(The man he was most upset about)
- I saw his expression! - Did you guess correctly?
Jae Seok was very intuitive.
(Super relieved)
The moment I said it could be Ssaebssaeb,
his expression totally changed.
- That's when I knew for sure. - Hey.
During the Chunhyang...
(They thought it was nonsense, but the quality was on point.)
- and Byun Hak Do episode, - That's the one.
- Jae Seok guessed it right. - Exactly.
He knew it was Se Chan.
I knew it.
Hold on.
- Yang Se Chan. - What about me?
(He was the spy.)
The look in your eyes...
- What? - What did he do?
You're suddenly saying it's me?
Hold on.
- You. - It's not the three empty heads.
- Hey. - It really isn't me.
- It's not me. - Even before...
(He was the spy too.)
- Yang Se Chan. - It's not me.
- It's Haha. - How many meals did you have?
It's not me.
- Yang Se Chan. - How can you assume it's me...
(They have the same faces again.)
just because one of them is unmarried?
When Jae Seok suspected me,
(Jae Seok nearly caught the embezzler with his sharp eye.)
I couldn't help making that same face.
- My gosh. - I knew it.
All right. The two embezzlers have won...
(The two embezzlers who won...)
assorted Korean pork, a classic team dinner staple.
(get a Korean pork set.)
- Thank you. - That's the best.
Aside from the embezzlers...
(The two embezzlers...)
and Jae Seok, who figured out who they were,
(and Jae Seok will not be punished.)
- Nice! - everyone else gets the penalty.
- Jae Seok, nice. - Congratulations.
Jae Seok, you almost caught me again.
- Those guys... - I know.
- They need to be taught a lesson. - A lesson.
For today's penalty,
a bucket of water...
(Today's penalty: Getting splashed)
will be dumped on you to wake you up.
Bring in the stools.
(Penalty takers: Haha, Ji Hyo, Hye Jun, Woo Min,)
See how it feels, Hye Jun.
(Seok Jin, Ye Eun, Jong Kook)
One, two, three.
Thank you!
(Splash)
Oh, my gosh!
- Gosh! - It's so cool.
(A photoshoot)
Gosh!
Isn't it nice?
- It's refreshing. - It's so nice!
(Calming his burning anger caused by the embezzlers)
- That was great. - Yes!
I want to jump into the water.
- That was nice. - Gosh.
- It's so nice! - Nice and dry.
(We'd like to thank Kang Hoon, Hye Jun, and Woo Min...)
- Let's stay dry today. - Let's stay dry today.
(for being the best employees.)
- What's this? - Where are we going?
(An unknown rich chairman...)
- What is this place? - Can't the rich crush the cops?
(has conquered the dark side.)
Who's this?
- Someone's coming. - It's SBS.
(The "Flex X Cop" team is here to arrest the money-mad chairman.)
- Oh, gosh. - Bo Hyun looks...
(Rich charisma)
You took six of mine.
(You took six of mine.)
I don't stand a chance against him.
(He even manages to tease the veteran members.)
- It's Bo Hyun. - You look cool, Bo Hyun.
(Ahn Bo Hyun)
- Is it your first time? - It's her first variety show.
(The dark-horse aura)
- It's my first TV variety show. - For real?
(Jung Eun Chae)
(Yelping)
Is it Eun Chae or me?
(A clumsy dark horse)
It was like Whac-A-Mole.
(It was like Whac-A-Mole.)
- She hopped up like this. - Sang Jun and Shin Bi too.
(A detective duo here to help their clumsy colleague!)
You're like Jae Seok. It's a matching look.
(Kang Sang Jun)
Right?
(Kim Shin Bi)
- Shin Bi's done for. - You infiltrated the rich.
(However)
You're an undercover detective.
(Spies have infiltrated the "Flex X Cop" team?)
You must hinder the detectives.
I was given a hefty mission.
(I was given a hefty mission.)
They stole the hint.
(They stole the hint.)
Oh, really?
(The rich versus the detectives)
- Then you... - That was...
(A tough power struggle)
- I think you're definitely the spy. - Me?
(Identify the enemy within.)
- There's this too. - We must find handcuffs.
(The chairman's gang is after the money.)
It's on the first floor?
(The detectives struggle to stop them.)
- You're ripping name tags? - Why run?
(The rich versus the detectives)
- Why run? - Do you have handcuffs?
(Who will take the case of cash?)
Stay still for three minutes.
- It's really not me. - Film this.
(Undercover Flex Versus Cops, 6:10pm, Sunday)
(Running Man)